music
音楽
Today I am honored to introduce today's speaker, Professor Xie Shiliang
本日は、講演者の謝世良教授を紹介できることを光栄に思います。
Professor Xie is an artist-scientist
謝教授は芸術家兼科学者です
He graduated from the Faculty of Medicine, National Yang Ming University
国立陽明大学医学部卒業
Afterwards, he went to Oxfern University of Liukin University in the UK to obtain a Ph.D.
その後、イギリスのリューキン大学オックスファーン大学に留学し、博士号を取得しました。
in immunology
免疫学では
Then I went to Stanford University in the United States to talk to a master of immunization there.
それから私は米国のスタンフォード大学に行き、そこの予防接種の達人に話を聞きました。
do PhD and research
博士号を取得して研究する
After returning to China, I went to Yangming University to talk to the Agricultural Federation
中国に帰国後、陽明大学に行って農業連盟と話をしました。
i am a professor there
私はそこの教授です
I have been making professors since I was a teaching assistant
私はティーチングアシスタントの頃から教授を務めてきました
He also served as the director of the immunization center there
彼はそこで予防接種センターの所長も務めました
And the director of Linchuan Medical Research Institute
そして林川医学研究所の所長
In 2013, he was the former dean of the hospital
2013年、彼は元病院長だった
Dean of Weng Jihui
ウェン・ジフイ社長
Recruited to Genome Research Center
ゲノム研究センターに採用
Course Specific Fellows
コース固有のフェロー
Professor Xie has a wide range of interests
謝教授の興味は非常に幅広いです
It is important that your focus is still on the immune and inflammatory response
引き続き免疫反応と炎症反応に焦点を当てることが重要です
in the early days
初めの頃
He's working on a molecule called DCR3
彼は DCR3 と呼ばれる分子を研究しています
I think he just mentioned
彼は今言ったと思います
interested in
に興味がある
did a lot of fun there
そこでとても楽しかったです
and some important discoveries
そしていくつかの重要な発見
He just shared with me
彼はちょうど私にシェアしてくれました
Some recent results
最近の結果
he's very exciting
彼はとても興奮しています
maybe he'll say something
たぶん彼は何か言うだろう
In addition, after arriving at the Chinese Medicine Hospital about a few years ago,
また、数年ほど前に中医病院に来てからは、
He became interested in Tang Science
彼は唐の科学に興味を持ちました
So he went into a
そこで彼は、
Research on a condensin we call C-Type
Cタイプと呼ばれるコンデンシンの研究
One of the lectins is C-Lac5
レクチンの 1 つは C-Lac5 です。
It's also his topic today
それは今日の彼の話題でもある
From there he found that this was
そこから彼はこれが
Dengue virus receptor
デングウイルス受容体
Then he goes through this receptor
それから彼はこの受容体を通過します
dengue virus
デング熱ウイルス
This nucleic acid virus can cause some very serious reactions in our body
この核酸ウイルスは、私たちの体内で非常に深刻な反応を引き起こす可能性があります。
So he also found out that he did
それで彼もまた、自分がそうしていたことに気づきました
If the virus can be combined with the receptor and can be inhibited
ウイルスが受容体と結合して阻害できれば
to suppress these reactions
これらの反応を抑えるために
This article was published in the magazine "Domination"
この記事は雑誌「ドミネーション」に掲載されました。
received international attention
国際的な注目を集めた
also got some patents
いくつかの特許も取得しています
this is indeed
これは確かに
It can be said that it has received a famous work
有名な作品を受賞したと言えます
But this was already
しかし、これはすでに
In this area has already received great attention
この分野はすでに大きな注目を集めています
He has received numerous awards for his words in Taiwan
彼の言葉は台湾で数々の賞を受賞している
including the Ministry of Science and Technology
科学技術省も含めて
Should be a research award for contact research
接触研究には研究賞を与えるべきだ
Then Ministry of Education Academic Award
当時文部大臣学術賞受賞
Ministry of Education's National Award
国民文部大臣賞
Every year, one or two can get
毎年1人か2人がもらえる
Contributions in Taiwan in addition to his own research
自身の研究のほか、台湾での貢献もある
He also has the talent of this leadership
彼はこのリーダーシップの才能も持っています
Then he was also responsible for Taiwan's immunology exchanges with the United States
その後、台湾と米国の免疫学交流の責任者も務めました。
Head of the American Society for Immunology
米国免疫学会会長
so i think today we are very happy
だから今日はとても幸せだと思います
He was able to share with us some of his recent
彼は最近のことの一部を私たちに共有することができました
Academic research and achievements
学術研究と成果
So let's welcome Professor Xie Xuechang
それでは謝学昌教授をお迎えしましょう
First of all, I would like to thank Vice President Liu Bodong for his introduction
まず最初に、紹介していただいた副社長Liu Bodongに感謝したいと思います。
Then I would also like to thank the Solemn Academy for inviting me here
それから、私をここに招待してくれた Solemn Academy にも感謝したいと思います。
Share the results of our research with you
私たちの研究結果をあなたと共有してください
Thanks
ありがとう
I would like to thank all ladies and gentlemen and the students who came to perform
演奏に来てくださった紳士淑女の皆様、そして生徒の皆様に感謝申し上げます。
Come to Academia Sinica at such a late hour
こんな遅い時間に中央研究院に来てください
We were very moved after listening to the speech
私たちはスピーチを聞いてとても感動しました
I want to introduce this topic to you today
今日はこの話題を紹介したいと思います
cytokine storm
サイトカインストーム
It's actually quite a coincidence
実はかなりの偶然なんです
Because before everyone assumes you remember
誰もがあなたが覚えていると思う前に
In 2003, Taiwan had this Sauce
2003年、台湾にはこのソースがありました
when Sauce comes
ソースが来ると
Everyone should be impressed
誰もが感動するはずです
At that time, the hundred-page depression could not go out
あの時、百ページの憂鬱は消えなかった
I still remember one time I drove to the 101 hair line
101ヘアラインまで車で行った時のことを今でも覚えています
empty with no one
誰もいなくて空っぽ
so you know that flush is very big
フラッシュが非常に大きいことがわかります
Then our AA chief at the time
当時のAAチーフ
Also one of our anti-kill Kazuo
私たちのアンチキルカズオの一人でもあります
Chief Arborist
主任樹木医
I don't know if you have no impression
印象に残っていないのかはわかりませんが、
At that time, the chief arborist called me
その時、樹木医長から電話があった。
he just said
彼はちょうど言った
Professor Xie, you are a person doing immunology research in Taiwan
謝先生は台湾で免疫学の研究をされている方ですね
Then you come and give us a speech saying
それからあなたは来て私たちにこうスピーチします
How Cytoheptin Storm Produces
サイトヘプチン ストームがどのように発生するか
i was young
私は若かった
I just want to say that there is a network
私が言いたいのは、ネットワークがあるということだけです
Although I don't do cytoheptin storm
サイトヘプチンストームはやってないけど
I'm going to look up books
本を調べてみます
It's okay to study and give a speech, right?
勉強してスピーチするのは大丈夫ですよね？
I'll say without hesitation
迷わず言います
no problem
問題ない
After I finish speaking, I will
話し終えたら、こうします
I regret it
私はそれを後悔します
because i go back at night
夜に帰るから
When I started to search the book, I found that
本を探し始めたところ、次のことが分かりました。
This message is really lacking
このメッセージは本当に欠けています
Where did this Cytoheptin come from?
このサイトヘプチンはどこから来たのでしょうか?
Although we all know the virus
ウイルスのことは誰もが知っていますが、
how to produce heparin
ヘパリンを生成する方法
eliciting this immune response is clearly
この免疫反応を引き起こすことは明らかです
But Cytoheptin is still not clear
しかし、サイトヘプチンはまだ明らかではありません
So a crisis is an opportunity
だから危機はチャンスだ
So from now on I want to say
だからこれから言いたいのは
then i should explore
それなら探索してみようかな
Why do viruses cause cytoheptin storms
なぜウイルスはサイトヘプチン・ストームを引き起こすのか
Why does it cause panic among humans
なぜ人間にパニックを引き起こすのか
or cause death
あるいは死を引き起こす
the most important thing is to say
最も重要なことは言うことです
do we have a way
方法はありますか
to overcome this virus
このウイルスを克服するために
cytogenetic storm
細胞遺伝学的嵐
So all this research because it's a chance call
つまり、この調査はすべて偶然の出会いだからです
then a bad decision
それなら悪い決断だ
led to the research I did today
今日の研究につながりました
before the disease
病気の前に
let's talk about
まずは話しましょう
our body
私たちの体
How to maintain a steady state
定常状態を維持する方法
And what is our relationship to the inflammatory response?
そして、炎症反応と私たちの関係は何でしょうか？
A person in a so-called healthy state of our body
いわゆる健康な身体状態にある人
Let's call it a school of literature
それを文学部と呼びましょう
Those who study biology probably know
生物学を勉強している人なら知っていると思いますが、
In biology we call it home-news-stasis
生物学ではこれをホームニュース停滞と呼びます
What about when stimulated by various reasons?
さまざまな理由で刺激を受けた場合はどうでしょうか？
Our bodies are dissatisfied with all kinds of receptors
私たちの体はあらゆる種類の受容体に不満を持っています
You can call it a receptor
受容体と呼んでもいいでしょう
It can also be called receptor in English
英語では受容体とも呼ばれます
Or sensee is fine
それとも先生でも大丈夫です
Basically it feels the presence of these stimuli
基本的にこれらの刺激の存在を感じます
when stimulated
刺激されると
you get an inflammatory reaction
炎症反応が起こる
In the end, tissue repair will be fine.
最終的には組織の修復はうまくいきます。
I think this is anytime
これはいつでもあると思います
happens all the time
いつも起こる
Just like we now our environment is full of
今の私たちと同じように、私たちの環境には
various bacterial viruses
さまざまな細菌ウイルス
Especially now that many influenza viruses
特に今はインフルエンザウイルスが多くなっているので、
in contagion
伝染病で
Many people have no symptoms
無症状の人も多い
because when your body feels its presence
なぜなら、あなたの体がその存在を感じるとき
you have a little inflammation
あなたは少し炎症を起こしています
What about after inflammation?
炎症が起きた後はどうでしょうか？
The final purpose is to return to a constant state
最終的な目的は一定の状態に戻ることです
So in a controllable
したがって、制御可能な状態で
under inflammatory reaction
炎症反応下にある
we call the so-called
私たちはいわゆる
Physiological inflammatory response
生理的炎症反応
What is the purpose of the physiological inflammatory response?
生理学的炎症反応の目的は何ですか?
it's trying to go back to what's called a constant state
いわゆる定常状態に戻ろうとしている
So in this state
それでこの状態で
You don't have to go to the hospital to see a doctor
医師の診察を受けるために病院に行く必要はありません
you just hurt
あなたはただ傷つけただけです
just drink some hot water and take a rest
お湯飲んで休んでください
we're back to what's called a constant state
いわゆる定常状態に戻ります
But what if our body
しかし、もし私たちの体が
If this inflammatory response is so perfect
この炎症反応が完璧なら
Then we don't need a hospital
そうすれば病院は要らない
You don't need to go to the doctor
医者に行く必要はありません
The doctor is out of work again
医者がまた仕事を休みました
so we need to know
だから私たちは知る必要がある
Why Inflammation Can Sometimes Cause Problems
炎症が時々問題を引き起こす理由
So from doing this tell you guys
それで、これを行うことで皆さんに伝えます
The inflammatory reaction is actually a
実は炎症反応というのは、
complex a vascular an inflammatory response
複合体、血管、炎症反応
Because we are in Zhouzhiao
周庄にいるから
A characteristic of an inflammatory response is redness, swelling, heat, and pain
炎症反応の特徴は、発赤、腫れ、熱感、痛みです。
why is it red
なぜ赤いのか
It is the increase of blood flow in our blood vessels
それは血管内の血流の増加です
it will be swollen
腫れるでしょう
It is the increase in the permeability of our blood vessel currency
それは私たちの血管通貨の透過性の増加です
This is very important
これはとても重要です
That is to say, we usually have a lot of
つまり、私たちは通常、たくさんのものを持っています
fluid in blood vessels
血管内の液体
But when you have a lot of inflammation
しかし、炎症がひどい場合には、
The permeability of your blood vessel coins will increase
血管の浸透性が高まります
So some liquid will come out
そうすると液体が出てきます
if you run outside
外を走る
This tissue will swell
この組織は腫れます
Inflammation that is in the area
その領域の炎症
its swelling is fine
腫れは大丈夫です
It's just that the mouth may be swollen.
ただ口が腫れる可能性もあります。
Then fatter people like me
それから私のような太った人は
It may be a little swollen and you can't see it.
少し腫れていて見えないこともあります。
but
しかし
Huayin reaction blessing is the whole body
華陰反応祝福は全身です
that's serious
それは深刻です
Because it means that you have a lot of fluid all over your body
体中に水分がたくさんあるということなので、
Will flow from the blood vessel into the adjacent soft tissue
血管から隣接する軟組織に流れます
what will happen at this time
このとき何が起こるでしょうか
lower blood pressure
血圧を下げる
Will go into shock and die
ショックを受けて死ぬだろう
So powerful flower shade reaction
とても強力な花陰反応
it causes death from shock
ショック死を引き起こす
The main reason is that the single use of blood vessel currency has increased
主な理由は、血管コインの単独使用が増加したことです。
Inflammation has two other characteristics:
炎症には他にも 2 つの特徴があります。
This is basically the separation from the cells
これは基本的に細胞からの分離です
a prostaglandin
プロスタグランジン
Called Posagranding is related
ポサグランディングと呼ばれるものが関係しています
what are the common factors
共通要素は何ですか
Will they have a negative reaction together?
彼らは一緒に否定的な反応を起こすでしょうか？
we generally know to say
私たちは一般的にこう言うことを知っています
exotic organisms
外来生物
But it's easiest to have a negative reaction together
でも一緒に否定的な反応をするのが一番簡単だ
So viruses, bacteria,
つまり、ウイルスや細菌、
All kinds of vitamins will
あらゆる種類のビタミンが
But the yin reaction is not
しかし、陰の反応はそうではありません
Only foreign bacteria will react negatively together
外来細菌のみが一緒に否定的に反応します
Substances in the body can also cause inflammation
体内の物質も炎症を引き起こす可能性があります
For example, if your body is subjected to physical or
たとえば、あなたの体が物理的または
or mechanical impact
または機械的衝撃
tissue is injured
組織が損傷している
after the injury
怪我の後
Our injured tissues and cells will
私たちの傷ついた組織や細胞は、
generate some danger signals
何らかの危険信号を生成する
also stimulates an inflammatory response
炎症反応も刺激します
what about the other one
もう一つはどうですか
your physical stuff
あなたの物理的なもの
such as uric acid
尿酸などの
We all have uric acid in our blood
私たちの血液中には尿酸が存在します
it is part of our body
それは私たちの体の一部です
In theory, it should not produce an inflammatory reaction.
理論的には、炎症反応を引き起こすことはありません。
but
しかし
When our uric acid concentration is high to
尿酸濃度が高くなると、
after a degree
学位を取得した後
it crystallizes
結晶化する
Crystallization for our body
私たちの体の結晶化
it violates the original
それは原作に違反します
steady state
定常状態
because it exceeds the standard it should have
本来あるべき基準を超えているから
so it starts from a
だからそれはから始まります
After turning into a crystal?
クリスタルになった後は？
our body knows
私たちの体は知っています
The body is not normal
体が正常ではない
so our bodily receptors recognize it
私たちの身体受容体がそれを認識します
Then there is also an inflammatory reaction
そうすると炎症反応も起こります
So this is called
それでこれは呼ばれます
sterile inflammatory response
無菌性炎症反応
So after the inflammatory reaction?
炎症反応の後は？
if it disappears soon
すぐに消えてしまったら
then we won't have symptoms
そうすれば症状は出なくなるよ
But if it continues to inflame
でも炎症が続くと
That of course can cause serious symptoms
もちろん重篤な症状を引き起こす可能性もあります
that can cause more serious symptoms
より深刻な症状を引き起こす可能性がある
Generally everyone is familiar with
一般的には誰もが知っている
It's all kinds of viruses
あらゆる種類のウイルスです
Or this East
あるいはこの東
or say some plum fungus
あるいは梅菌のことを言う
their various bacteria
彼らのさまざまな細菌
When infected, it causes an inflammatory reaction
感染すると炎症反応を起こします
So in this case
したがって、この場合には
Assuming that the amount of bacteria is small
菌の量が少ないと仮定すると
or when the amount of virus is low
またはウイルスの量が少ない場合
or our body has antibodies
あるいは私たちの体には抗体がある
when able to control it
それをコントロールできるようになったら
we'll still go to the left
私たちはまだ左に行きます
Response to business
ビジネスへの対応
fever headache
発熱 頭痛
we pressed it down later
後でそれを押しました
Just organize the humiliation and you'll be fine.
屈辱を整理するだけで大​​丈夫です。
But the bigger challenge we feel is
しかし、私たちが感じているより大きな課題は、
so-called pathological inflammatory response
いわゆる病的炎症反応
It's when the inflammatory response doesn't stop
炎症反応が止まらないときです
In the end the tissue will be injured
最終的には組織が損傷することになる
tissue injury
組織損傷
after the injury
怪我の後
it's not going to tinker
それはいじくり回しません
It's called repairing.
いわゆる修理です。
If my liver cells are damaged
肝細胞が損傷している場合
I use liver cells to supplement
肝細胞を使って補います
then no problem
それなら問題ない
my skin cells
私の皮膚細胞
When I get hurt, I replace it with skin cells
怪我をすると皮膚細胞と入れ替わる
pen cells to mend
ペンセルを修復する
What we least like to see is
私たちが最も見たくないものは、
fibrosis
線維症
fibrosis means
線維化とは
when we hurt
私たちが傷ついたとき
Our body has a cell
私たちの体には細胞があります
fibroblast
線維芽細胞
called fibroblast
線維芽細胞と呼ばれる
What about when you use it for repairs?
修理などで使用する場合はどうでしょうか？
it
それ
will cause many problems
多くの問題を引き起こすでしょう
First
初め
from the most superficial
最も表面的なことから
You accidentally got scratched here with a knife
誤ってここをナイフで傷つけてしまった
Break down
壊す
why break down
なぜ壊れるのか
because you patched it with
パッチを当てたから
Fibroblast
線維芽細胞
So a bar will be generated
したがってバーが生成されます
it's on the skin
それは皮膚の上にある
there is a bar
バーがあります
Never mind
どうでも
girls may hate
女の子は嫌がるかもしれない
but boys can be sexy
でも男の子もセクシーになることができる
a lot of bar
たくさんのバー
but this thing
しかし、このこと
If it happens to your liver
肝臓に起こったら
that's not sexy at all
それは全然セクシーじゃない
it's serious
それは深刻です
what is it called
それはなんと呼ばれていますか
it's called cirrhosis
それは肝硬変と呼ばれます
If the lungs are inflamed
肺が炎症を起こしている場合
What about after pneumonia?
肺炎の後はどうでしょうか？
Fibrosis of the lungs
肺の線維化
then pulmonary fibrosis
次に肺線維症
What are the consequences of fibrosis?
線維症の影響は何ですか?
is the function is gone
機能がなくなってしまったのか
so there is nothing you can do in your liver
だから肝臓ではどうしようもない
carry out this metabolism
この新陳代謝を行う
even as it gets hard
たとえ難しくなっても
Then the blood doesn't pass easily
そうなると血液が出にくくなります
Then the pressure in the hepatic portal vein increases
すると肝臓門脈内の圧力が上昇します
easy to bleed
出血しやすい
then in the lungs
それから肺の中で
when you have fibrosis
線維症があるとき
Then the lungs can't breathe
そうなると肺は呼吸できなくなる
that's like a lot of vacuuming
それはたくさんの掃除機をかけるようなものです
The family likes to go there
家族はそこに行くのが好きです
Like Jiufen
九份のように
Jiufen used to use that old miner
九份は昔、あの古い鉱山労働者を使っていました
Did you see them playing chess?
彼らがチェスをしているのを見ましたか?
Bring oxygen because he plays chess
彼はチェスをするので酸素を持ってきてください
by some wet lika in this ore
この鉱石の中の濡れたリカによって
it causes an inflammatory response
それは炎症反応を引き起こします
fibrosis
線維症
So this is the most serious problem
つまり、これが最も深刻な問題なのです
So I use this example
そこで私はこの例を使います
you can tell
教えてもいいよ
this inflammatory reaction
この炎症反応
our worst concern is to say
私たちの最大の懸念はこう言うことです
he can't stop
彼は止まらない
Then besides saying
それから言うだけでなく
In addition to causing immediate shock
即座にショックを与えるだけでなく、
even if you survive
たとえ生き残ったとしても
You still have this fibrosis
あなたはまだこの線維症を持っています
So in the past SARS infected patients
つまり、過去にはSARSに感染した患者がいた
even after some of it survives
たとえ一部が生き残った後でも
it will have side effects
副作用があるだろう
That is, its respiratory function will be reduced
つまり呼吸機能が低下してしまうのです
Mostly caused by fibrosis
ほとんどが線維症によって引き起こされます
in causing all fibrosis
あらゆる線維症の原因となる
or be able to transpose the reaction inside
または内部の反応を置き換えることができます
the main one
メインのもの
The most important factor is
最も重要な要素は
There is a class of protein
タンパク質には種類がある
we call cytokines
私たちはサイトカインと呼んでいます
Cytokines are
サイトカインは
when the cells of our body
私たちの体の細胞が
especially our
特に私たちの
water polo cell
水球細胞
Especially the protagonist we are going to talk about today
特に今日お話しする主人公
giant cells
巨式細胞
being received
受け取られている
after infection
感染之後
it gets a virus
ウイルスに感染する
direct stimulus
直接的な刺激
cell it will
セル、そうなります
produce a variety of cytokines
さまざまなサイトカインを生成する
Physiological functions of chemokines are basically good
ケモカインの生理機能は基本的に良好
The first one, for example, this one is called exorcising prostitutes
一つ目は、例えばこれは売春婦の祓いというものです。
Wait a minute, I will zoom in and see if there is Chinese written
ちょっと待ってください。中国語で書かれているかどうかを拡大して確認します
It will attract a lot of cotton-padded cells
綿が詰まった細胞をたくさん引き寄せます
carry out an inflammatory response
炎症反応を起こす
But it also contributes to the so-called self-inflicted
しかし、それはいわゆる自傷行為の一因にもなります。
The one that more strongly contributes to the increase of repairing diseases is called
病気の修復の増加により強く寄与するものは、と呼ばれます。
Inflammatory prostaglandin This is called Proinfotour Satellite
炎症性プロスタグランジン これはプロインフォツアーサテライトと呼ばれます
Of course it also produces interferon
もちろんインターフェロンも生成します
That interferon is basically good
インターフェロンは基本的には良いです
Because we all know that after interferon is produced
インターフェロンが生成された後は誰もが知っているので、
It inhibits the occurrence of viruses
ウイルスの発生を抑制します
So this inflammatory reaction we both hate and love
つまり、この炎症反応は私たちが嫌いでもあり、愛するものでもあります
because you don't have an inflammatory response
炎症反応がないから
you don't produce an interferon
インターフェロンを生成しない
But what about when you have inflammation
しかし、炎症がある場合はどうでしょうか
You will also have these bad for your health
これらも健康に悪影響を及ぼします
Some cellular techniques that increase vascular permeability
血管透過性を高めるいくつかの細胞技術
If a cell has a large amount of technology
セルに大量のテクノロジーが搭載されている場合
It will cause a G
Gが発生します
cause damage to the organization
組織に損害を与える
cause excessive inflammation
過剰な炎症を引き起こす
In addition, I said that the swelling of the blood vessels
また、血管の腫れとも言いましたが、
inflationary increase
インフレの増加
Then I will use an example below
次に、以下の例を使用します
you can tell
教えてもいいよ
You don't know if this is changed to a film
これが映画になるかどうかはわかりません
When we usually have an inflammatory response
私たちが通常炎症反応を起こしているとき
all go for a while
みんなしばらく行ってください
The patient is most afraid of seeing swelling
患者は腫れを見ることを最も恐れます
so you see swelling
それで腫れが見えます
and then reflect for a while
そして少し反省してから
Patients are most afraid of seeing this
患者はこれを見るのを最も恐れています
a piece of white
白い部分
Said there was water in it
水が入っているとのことでした
You probably know there's a lot of water in here
ここに水がたくさんあるのはご存知かと思いますが、
Why
なぜ
Because when it's time to shine
輝く時が来たから
high water density
水密度高
he can't penetrate
彼は侵入できない
so if you see
それで見たら
There are many white things in it
白いものがたくさん入っています
We knew there was a lot of liquid in here
ここに大量の液体があることはわかっていました
How did that liquid come here?
その液体はどうやってここに来たのですか？
now you understand
あなたは理解した
is an inflammatory reaction
炎症反応です
This is typical in a SARS patient
これはSARS患者では典型的なことである
what happened
どうしたの
after being infected
感染した後
Inflammation of the entire lung
肺全体の炎症
so when his whole lung
それで彼の肺全体が
when full of liquid
液体がいっぱいのとき
Of course the patient
もちろん患者さんも
he can't breathe
彼は息ができない
we are going to put him
私たちは彼を置くつもりです
sent to the interactive ward
インタラクティブ病棟に送られる
when it was listed
上場されたとき
After the patient was sent to the interactive ward
患者が対話型病棟に送られた後
everyone thinks
誰もが思う
interactive ward can
インタラクティブな病棟ができる
keep him alive
彼を生かしておく
Then the patient recovered
その後患者は回復した
then please
それではお願いします
how is the patient
患者はどうですか
do our doctors have medicine
私たちの医師は薬を持っていますか
symptomatic treatment
対症療法
is also a treatment
治療法でもあります
But there is no cure
しかし、治療法はありません
So the patient later
それで患者は後で
how good is he
彼はどれくらい良いですか
or you should try to say
あるいはこう言ってみるといいでしょう
So how do we treat this patient?
では、この患者をどのように治療すればよいのでしょうか?
Basically we have no cure
基本的に治療法はありません
but what can a doctor do
しかし医者に何ができるだろうか
we give him a way
私たちは彼に道を与えます
supportive care
支持療法
That is to say
つまり
He couldn't breathe
彼は息ができなかった
So after we get to the interactive ward
インタラクティブ病棟に着いたら
we give him a high pressure
私たちは彼に高圧をかける
hyperbaric therapy
高圧療法
High ammonia oxygen because he is also under a lot of pressure
大きなプレッシャーにもさらされているため、アンモニウム酸素が高くなっている
He's high on oxygen and forced to pour it in.
彼は酸素が豊富で、酸素を注入することを余儀なくされました。
Although there is water
水はあるのに
I still put oxygen in
まだ酸素を入れてます
Let his lungs still be able to give up
彼の肺がまだ諦められるようにしましょう
So basically send it to the hospital
基本的には病院に送ってください
Our most important thing is the sustainer of the phenomenon of life.
私たちにとって最も重要なことは、生命現象を維持することです。
supportive care
支持療法
Just let him go through this dangerous period
この危険な時期を彼に経験させてあげてください
So a lot of time to the hospital
病院に行くのにかなりの時間がかかるので、
They say it's dangerous
彼らはそれは危険だと言う
to go to the education ward
教育病棟に行く
To bless him through the dangerous period
危険な時期を乗り越えるために彼を祝福するために
that's all
それで全部です
well the problem is
さて問題は
After that dangerous period
その危険な時期を経て
he's fine, right?
彼は大丈夫ですよね？
the question is how good
問題はどれくらい良いかです
We still have no medicine
まだ薬がない
just what
いったい何
is our immune system
私たちの免疫システムは
Let him heal slowly
ゆっくり治してあげましょう
i just said
私はちょうど言いました
I said it in the first film
最初の映画でも言ってたけど
The purpose of our entire inflammatory response
私たちの炎症反応全体の目的
not to kill the patient
患者を殺さないように
The purpose of the immune response is to return to a steady state
免疫反応の目的は定常状態に戻ることです
Just saying that sometimes the virus is too strong
ウイルスが強すぎる場合があるとだけ言っておきます
Or our body immunity is too weak
あるいは体の免疫力が弱すぎる
When the inflammatory response cannot be stopped
炎症反応を止められない場合
He's going to cause a lot of inflammation
かなりの炎症を引き起こすだろう
then cause death
それから死を引き起こす
but once you get over that
でもそれを乗り越えたら
when each system slowly
各システムが遅いとき
because we are infected
私たちは感染しているから
we develop antibodies
私たちは抗体を開発します
Our T cells activate
私たちのT細胞は活性化します
So wait until our body
だから私たちの体が終わるまで待ってください
after this difficult time
この困難な時期を経て
We have time to let our body's T cells
私たちには体のT細胞を解放する時間があります
After slowly activating that antibody
その抗体をゆっくりと活性化させた後、
We can slowly suppress the virus
ウイルスをゆっくりと抑えることができる
avoid or die
避けるか死ぬか
So a treatment like this
そこでこのような治療法
Let's think of a way
方法を考えてみましょう
If there is an acute infection
急性感染症がある場合
Then there are 10,000 people in Taiwan
そうすると台湾には1万人がいる
or 100,000 people infected
あるいは10万人が感染する
when respirators are needed
人工呼吸器が必要なとき
what to do
何をすべきか
We're melting away so big
私たちはとても大きく溶けていきます
The melt away is sensitive to the virus
溶けたものを取り除き、ウイルスに敏感になりましょう
Inside the bed of the interactive virus
インタラクティブウイルスのベッドの中
no more than 200 beds
ベッド数は200台以下
The whole of Taiwan adds up to about
台湾全土を合計すると約
I think there are probably thousands of beds at most
おそらく多くて数千のベッドがあると思います
One or two thousand beds would be great
ベッドが1000か2000あればすごいだろう
then we have so many people
それなら私たちにはたくさんの人がいます
How to deal with infection
感染症にどう対処するか
So this gave me an idea at the time
それで、これは当時私にアイデアを与えました
That is, do we have a way?
つまり、方法はあるのでしょうか？
to be aware of this
これに気づくこと
pronunciation response
発音反応
then let it tide over
それからそれを乗り越えさせてください
What about after the hard times?
困難な時期の後にはどうでしょうか？
it doesn't have to be in the aftercare ward
アフターケア病棟にいる必要はない
As long as we have a miracle drug
特効薬がある限り
type in
入力してください
Then its pronunciation response is
その場合、その発音応答は次のようになります。
suppressed to the point where we can accept
受け入れられる程度に抑えられている
won't make our range
私たちの範囲には入りません
Then gradually the patient will
すると徐々に患者さんは、
recover that's fine
回復して、大丈夫です
it was a dream
それは夢だった
Okay, so what about the cytokine storm?
さて、それではサイトカインストームについてはどうでしょうか？
basically
基本的
it is the cause of death
それが死因です
then we today
それから私たちは今日
Although SARS passed
SARSは去ったものの、
we are still very heavy on it
私たちはまだそれに非常に重荷を負っています
Because of
なぜなら
There are many new viruses
新しいウイルスもたくさんある
For example, after the end of SARS
例えば、SARS終息後
It can still be called MERS now
まだMERSと呼ばれる可能性があります
the other one is me
もう一人は私です
As you all know, there was a virus called H5N1 in Hong Kong a few years ago
皆さんご存知のとおり、数年前に香港でH5N1と呼ばれるウイルスが発生しました。
this is the flu
これはインフルエンザです
Or last year there was a Taiwanese H7N9
あるいは昨年は台湾のH7N9が発生しました
when they get this infection
彼らがこの感染症にかかると
same as lungs
肺と同じ
symptoms like this
このような症状
what about other than that
それ以外はどうですか？
There is a class of viruses called that cause this
これを引き起こすウイルスのクラスがあります。
So-called
所謂的
Virus of conjunctivitis
結膜炎のウイルス
we probably don't know
私たちはおそらく知りません
In Africa there is a man called Ebola
アフリカにはエボラと呼ばれる男がいる
after he got infected
彼が感染した後
will be a great one
素晴らしいものになるだろう
first blood course
最初の血液コース
The other one is in Taiwan
もう一人は台湾にいます
We will have a slightly degraded virus
わずかに劣化したウイルスが存在します
Our name is Denge virus
私たちの名前はデンジウイルスです
Denge virus?
デンジウイルス？
in general patients
一般の患者さんでは
He developed a fever with some symptoms
彼はいくつかの症状を伴って発熱した
He doesn't necessarily cause serious symptoms.
必ずしも重篤な症状を引き起こすわけではありません。
but in some people
しかし一部の人では
or in the elderly
あるいは高齢者の場合
after he was infected
彼が感染した後
he will cause class syndrome
彼は講義症候群を引き起こすだろう
basically like
基本的に好き
It's all because he has too much cytokines
それはすべてサイトカインが多すぎるためです
Bacteria will
細菌は
So we're thinking
そこで私たちは考えています
In the end cytokine storm
結局はサイトカインストーム
what is his molecular basis
彼の分子基盤は何ですか
How on earth did he overcome this problem
いったい彼はこの問題をどうやって克服したのか
So I take this picture again
それでまたこの写真を撮ります
take it out again
もう一度取り出してください
just found out
たった今わかった
why in the past
なぜ過去に
Many immunosuppressive drugs have
多くの免疫抑制剤には、
Then why can't this disease be cured?
では、なぜこの病気は治らないのでしょうか？
Okay, so what's the basic reason?
さて、それでは根本的な理由は何でしょうか？
Let me emphasize it again
もう一度強調しておきます
The cytokines we produce can be divided into three categories
私たちが生成するサイトカインは 3 つのカテゴリーに分類できます。
The first one is called heparin
最初のものはヘパリンと呼ばれます
What about heparin, it inhibits virus replication
ヘパリンはどうですか、ウイルスの複製を阻害します
that is good
それはいいです
But we pronounce the reaction
しかし、私たちは反応を表明します
At the same time, the so-called trigger inflammatory hormone is produced
同時に、いわゆるトリガー炎症ホルモンが生成されます。
It will increase the permeability of the vascular bottle
血管ボトルの透過性を高めます
it produces kimo liver
キモ肝を生み出す
Slightly degassing hormones so that the pronunciation is more responsive
発音がより反応しやすくなるように、ホルモンをわずかに脱気します。
so our problem
それで私たちの問題は
When we were in SARS
SARSのとき
I have thought of many ways
いろいろな方法を考えました
For example, someone said
たとえば、誰かが言いました
Let's get on steroids
ステロイドを使いましょう
Steroids down to suppress its immune system
免疫システムを抑制するためにステロイドを減らす
hyperphonic response
過度のアーティキュレーション
is this good
これでいいですか
not good what is the reason
良くない理由は何ですか
that's because
それは
When the steroids go down
ステロイドが減ると
all suppressed
すべて抑制された
You suppress the good and the bad, all of it
良いことも悪いこともすべて抑制してしまう
then we all know
それなら私たちは皆知っています
Moderate articulation response is required
中程度のアーティキュレーション応答が必要です
So using steroids is different
だからステロイドを使うのは違う
that some people say
と言う人もいます
Now there is a class of
現在有一類的
There is a very powerful
非常に強力なものがあります
The head of the game is called TNF
ゲームの主役はTNFと呼ばれます
can we suppress it
それを抑制できますか
Basically it doesn't work too well because the
基本的にはあまりうまく機能しないので、
When the cell gas storm is generated
セルガスストーム発生時
There are probably dozens of cytokines
おそらく数十のサイトカインが存在する
You can't just suppress one
片方だけを抑えることはできない
So what is the best way
それで、最善の方法は何ですか
the best way is
最良の方法は
you have a way
あなたには方法があります
You only selectively suppress
選択的に抑制するだけです
You keep this interferon going
あなたはこのインターフェロンを続けます
But you only put these trigger meta bases
ただし、これらのトリガーメタベースを配置するだけです
hold it back
それを我慢してください
then you separate the two
次に、その 2 つを分離します
Then it may be possible to achieve
そうすれば達成できるかも知れません
The effect of our treatment
当院の治療効果
So the biggest challenge is
したがって、最大の課題は
How to suppress only the trigger metafactor
トリガーメタファクターのみを抑制する方法
and compartmentalization factor
と区画化係数
then avoid inhibiting interferon
インターフェロンの阻害を避ける
So when the idea came up
それで、そのアイデアが浮かんだとき、
people say
人々は言います
you want to dream, right?
夢を見たいですよね？
The problem is this
問題はこれです
We are the most beautiful dreams
私たちは最も美しい夢です
Only with dreams can you have some imagination
夢があってこそ想像力を持つことができる
See if you can help me solve this problem
この問題の解決を手伝ってくれないか見てください
the problem with this
これの問題
question when i put it
私がポーズをとったときの質問
many people are interested
多くの人が興味を持っています
because now the whole world has
なぜなら今世界はそうしているからです
There are a lot of new infectious diseases
新しい感染症がたくさんあります
almost all diseases
ほぼすべての病気
It's all related to Cell Storm
それはすべてセルストームに関係しています
SARS, MERS, H5N1, common virus
SARS、MERS、H5N1、一般的なウイルス
I just talked about EBOLA
先ほどエボラ出血熱について話しました
it's all a problem
それはすべて問題だ
So as long as it can solve this problem
この問題を解決できる限り
It's not just about treating a virus
ウイルスを治療するだけではありません
It can treat many viruses
多くのウイルスを治療できる
resulting disease
結果として生じる病気
good
良い
So when I think about it next time
それで、次のことを考えたら
start experimenting
実験を始める
Just say that SARS is so serious
SARSは非常に深刻だとだけ言ってください
So we applied for the National Science Program
そこで私たちは国立科学プログラムに応募しました
Then what
じゃあ何
finally
ついに
The previous opportunity has come
前回のチャンスが来た
SARS is gone
SARSは去った
So when doing this research
したがって、この調査を行うとき、
a little frustrated
少しイライラした
don't want to be depressed
落ち込んだくない
I'm glad to say that SARS will be brought under control soon
SARSがすぐに制御されることを嬉しく思います
But the people who do the research are
しかし、研究をしている人たちは、
When you think you haven't even started
まだ始まってないと思ったら
he is too late
彼は遅すぎる
So then we thought
それで私たちは考えました
Let's find a comparison
比較を見つけてみましょう
Another virus for research
研究用の別のウイルス
yellow virus
黄色のウイルス
so prevent virus
だからウイルスを防ぐ
There are English called Pravy Viruses
英語ではPravy Virusesというウイルスがあります
that it contains a lot of viruses
ウイルスがたくさん含まれているということ
Including dengue virus is water to prevent viruses
デングウイルスを含むウイルスを防ぐ水です
Japanese old source virus is also to prevent virus
日本の古いソースウイルスもウイルスを防ぐ
And more common in the West
そして西洋ではもっと一般的です
A Cinnirohe virus called Wesnile
ウェスナイルと呼ばれるシンニロヘウイルス
There is also a recent very popular
最近大人気のものもございます
The virus that was very popular last year was called the Zika virus
昨年非常に流行したウイルスはジカウイルスと呼ばれていました
It's all Pravy Viruses
それはすべてPravyウイルスです
That's inside the dengue virus inside
それはデング熱ウイルスの内部です
There are probably all over the world
おそらく世界中にあるだろう
390 charming
390 魅力的
That's 390 million people
それは3億9千万人です
are threatened by dengue fever approximately every year
毎年デング熱の脅威にさらされています
Then 96 charming
それから96は魅力的です
a more serious symptom
さらに深刻な症状
country where it happens
それが起こる国
in warmer countries
暖かい国では
For example in this
たとえばこれでは
throughout the
全体で
Very serious in India
インドでは非常に深刻
And Southeast Asia
そして東南アジア
And Central and South America are very serious
そして中南米は非常に深刻です
then it is
それならそうです
it again causes a lot of real
それは再び多くの現実を引き起こします
some cause encephalitis
脳炎を引き起こすものもある
Everyone knows it's Japanese encephalitis.
それが日本脳炎であることは誰もが知っています。
Z card causes microcephaly encephalitis
Zカードが小頭症脳炎を引き起こす
But what we are more afraid of is the dengue graduates
しかし、私たちがもっと恐れているのは、デング熱卒業生です。
Those who graduated from dengue
デング熱から卒業した人たち
Because dengue virus has four types
デングウイルスには4種類あるので
So now there is no good vaccine
つまり今のところ良いワクチンはない
The vaccine made in the Philippines a few days ago
数日前にフィリピンで作られたワクチン
not very successful
あまり成功していない
And it makes the patient worse
そしてそれは患者をさらに悪化させます
so we're trying to say yes
だから私たちはイエスと言おうとしているのです
then we use dengue virus
それならデング熱ウイルスを使う
study as an example
例として勉強する
How does dengue virus cause cellular agent transfer
デング熱ウイルスはどのようにして細胞内感染を引き起こすのか
After dengue virus infection
デングウイルス感染後
It's basically inspired by Egyptian brindle
基本的にはエジプトのブリンドルからインスピレーションを受けています
this infected
この感染者
then it compares
それから比較します
Its special symptom is
その特殊な症状は、
when it is infected
感染したとき
it all flares up and breaks out
すべてが燃え上がり、爆発する
platelets then drop
その後血小板が低下する
The other body will be very painful
他の体はとても痛いでしょう
That's when it's more powerful when you go out of school
学校を出たときがより力強いのです
This is the tendency to go out of school
これが不登校の傾向です
It was found that the platelets decreased
血小板が減っていることが分かりました
then this place
それからこの場所
if you have some injuries
怪我をしている場合
the whole of this
これ全体
Running away after studying medicine is very scary
医学を勉強して逃げるのはとても怖い
What's more powerful are those children
あの子達の方が強いよ
Now when he has this inflammatory reaction all over his body
今、彼の体中に炎症反応が起きているとき、
wow he knew very humiliating reaction
すごい、彼はとても屈辱的な反応を知っていた
The whole body is very red
体全体が真っ赤です
it's very scary
とても怖いです
Then there is no special medicine to treat it.
そうなると、特別な治療法はありません。
So when we do this experiment
したがって、この実験を行うと、
how to think
どのように考えるか
how do we go about solving this problem
この問題をどう解決するか
that's like my first
それは私の最初のようなものです
The introduction to you is
あなたへの紹介は、
Our body wants to feel the inflammatory response
私たちの体は炎症反応を感じようとしています
It must be because he has a lot of this receptor on his back
背中にこの受容体がたくさんあるからに違いない
detected
検出されました
Then I drew these various shapes
それから私はこれらのさまざまな形を描きました
these English names
これらの英語の名前
It means that our organelles
それは私たちの細胞小器官が
There are various receptors
様々な受容体が存在する
on our blood oil
私たちの血の油について
So I had an idea at the time and said
そこで私はその時思いついてこう言いました
This virus will be very harmful
このウイルスは非常に有害になるだろう
cause an inflammatory response
炎症反応を引き起こす
will it be
そうなるだろうか
It stimulates these receptors on the cells
細胞上のこれらの受容体を刺激します
After stimulating these receptors
これらの受容体を刺激した後、
almost an inflammatory reaction
ほぼ炎症反応
To be able to tell who, say, dengue virus or Ebola virus combined with
デング熱ウイルスやエボラウイルスが誰と結合したかを知ることができるようにするには
Then I have a way to use a method to antibody or something
それなら、抗体か何かを取得する方法を使用する方法があります
suppress their irritation
彼らのイライラを抑える
Then the whole pronunciation response can be reduced
そうすれば、全体の発音反応を減らすことができます
it's a very simple idea
それはとてもシンプルなアイデアです
The idea is simple but it is difficult to implement
アイデアはシンプルですが、実行するのは難しいです
What are we going to do in order to do this experiment?
この実験を行うには何をするのでしょうか?
We're going to get it from the blood bank. I was at Yang Ming University at the time.
血液銀行から入手するのですが、当時私は陽明大学にいました。
That's the blood bank in Tamsui
それが淡水の血液銀行です
So my students often have to run into fresh water
そのため、私の生徒たちは頻繁に真水に遭遇しなければなりません
to get a patient's blood
患者の血液を採取する
We just had some educational cooperation
教育協力を行ったばかりです
If you say you want to camp, use it
キャンプしたいって言うなら使ってください
So with the patient's consent, we took some blood
そこで患者さんの同意を得て採血をしました。
Blood cells are separated from the blood through a series of complex processes
血球は一連の複雑なプロセスを経て血液から分離されます
After the blood cell, we will store it
血球採取後は保管いたします
We only need to deposit a specific labeled C14 POS cell
特定のラベルを付けた C14 POS セルをデポジットするだけで済みます
It's MarcoForge for giant cells
巨大細胞の MarcoForge です
Then we let it add cell technology
次に、細胞技術を追加させます
let it dedifferentiate
脱差別化させましょう
What do you do after splitting up?
別れた後は何をしますか？
we start from
から始めます
We know that the cell
私たちは細胞が
There must be many of these receptors
これらの受容体はたくさんあるはずです
So we use the techniques of molecular medicine
そこで私たちは分子医学の技術を利用します
we'll go get the inside
中を取りに行きます
RNA message
RNAメッセージ
just translate it into cDNA
それをcDNAに翻訳するだけです
then one by one
それから一つ一つ
Using a technique called PCR
PCRと呼ばれる技術を使用する
to amplify these genes
これらの遺伝子を増幅させるために
same as aquamarine
アクアマリンと同じ
get it out one by one
一つ一つ取り出して
One is not enough after getting it out
出したら1つじゃ足りない
Because of this G you have to turn it into a protein
この G があるため、タンパク質に変換する必要があります。
So we're using the offensive
だから私たちは攻撃的な手段を使っています
let's take it as an example
例として見てみましょう
this is a sensor
これはセンサーです
expressed in this cell
この細胞で発現される
We need to know it is to extract its RNA first
最初に RNA を抽出する必要があることを知る必要があります
because we all know
私たちは皆知っているから
Protein is converted from DNA to RNA
タンパク質はDNAからRNAに変換されます
Change PoTin
ポティンを変更する
so we pump it for RNA
そこで RNA をポンプで汲み上げます
after flipping it out
それをひっくり返した後
and then make it a cDNA
そしてそれをcDNAにします
Then bind to this part of the antibody
次に、抗体のこの部分に結合します
make it a fusion protein
融合タンパク質にする
it will be easy
それは簡単でしょう
This is just to prepare these things yourself
これは自分で用意するものです
It took almost two years
ほぼ2年かかりました
Then the experiment is easy to do
それなら実験は簡単です
But it costs a lot of money to do it.
しかし、それをやるには多額の費用がかかります。
When doing this experiment
この実験をするときに
i'm lucky
私はラッキーです
At that time, it was sprayed on this Dean Weng Qihui
その時、このディーン・ウェン・チーフイにスプレーされました
Dean Weng said it was a good idea
ディーン・ウェンはそれは良いアイデアだと言いました
worthy of encouragement
励ましに値する
So you have to have this bullet in war
だから戦争ではこの弾丸が必要だ
So he offered me some bullets
それで彼は私にいくつかの弾丸を提供した
we spent two years
私たちは2年間を過ごしました
Just do this thing and do nothing
これだけやって何もしない
finally these weapons
ついにこの武器が
Take these thirty or so proteins
これらの30ほどのタンパク質を摂取してください
make it one by one
一つ一つ作っていきます
took a very long time
とても長い時間がかかりました
when it's done
終わったら
This is the most tense moment
ここが一番緊張する瞬間です
Is that idea right or wrong?
その考えは正しいのでしょうか、それとも間違っているのでしょうか?
I can't make it right, I'm thinking wrong, what should I do?
正しくできない、間違った考えをしている、どうすればいいですか
so it's tense
だから緊張している
Of course we took two years to do it
もちろん、それをやるのに2年かかりました
It took a lot of time to support
サポートにとても時間がかかりました
After we made those Porting
これらの移植を行った後、
Let's do a very intense experiment
非常に激しい実験をしてみましょう
So we just put this
それで、これを置くだけです
Each black represents a different protein
それぞれの黒は異なるタンパク質を表します
Of course not only that much
もちろんそれ以上に
it's a simple statement
それは簡単な声明です
Just put dozens of proteins
数十種類のプロテインを入れるだけ
put it all on a plate
全部お皿に盛り付けて
Then put the virus on
それからウイルスを入れます
Then use antibodies to detect
次に、抗体を使用して検出します
is there any one
誰かいますか
made receptors
作られた受容体
will combine with it
それと組み合わせるでしょう
So this experiment is actually pretty bad.
つまり、この実験は実際にはかなりひどいものです。
Then one day when doing this kind of experiment
ある日、このような実験をしていたとき
Bosses are just as nervous as students
上司も学生と同じように緊張している
So we're in the lab
それで私たちは研究室にいます
Then finally after several failures
そして、いくつかの失敗を経て、ついに
One day my student came knocking on my door
ある日、生徒が私のドアをノックしてきました。
This Mr. Long is amazing after a long time
久しぶりにこのロングさんはすごいですね
Is the student doing well?
その生徒は元気ですか？
don't ask
聞かないでください
just look at him
ただ彼を見てください
Know the sound and frequency of knocking on the door
ドアをノックする音と頻度を知る
The one that knocks very slowly
非常にゆっくりとノックするもの
very listless
とても無気力な
Don't ask, it must be bad
聞かないでください、きっと悪いことです
knocking fast
早くノックする
must be a good result
良い結果になるはずです
found it strange
奇妙だと思いました
This student knocked on the door before
この学生は前にドアをノックしました
that's not the sound knock
それはノックの音ではありません
Knocking very briskly today
今日はノックがとても活発です
probably good news
おそらく良いニュース
I just invite him in
私は彼を招待するだけです
Then he showed me this picture
それから彼は私にこの写真を見せました
He said he saw
彼は見たと言った
There are three receptors that bind to him
彼に結合する受容体は 3 つあります
I am very happy to see this picture
この写真を見てとても嬉しいです
because the left-hand side of it is in two receptors
左側が 2 つの受容体にあるため
strong combination
強力な組み合わせ
this has been known in the past
これは以前から知られていた
He will combine with dengue virus
彼はデング熱ウイルスと結合するだろう
But he will only bond with him
でも彼は彼とだけ絆を結ぶだろう
He's just responsible for his run into the cell
彼には独房に逃げ込んだ責任があるだけだ
But he doesn't elicit the cell's response technology
しかし、彼は細胞の反応技術を引き出しません
what i see is this
私が見ているのはこれです
It always looks different from the students
学生とはいつも違うように見える
Students feel bad when they see this
これを見ると学生は気分が悪くなる
this combination is so low
この組み合わせは低すぎる
But after I saw this spirit
でもこの魂を見てからは
I'll look it up when I find it
見つけたら調べてみます
what on earth do
一体何をするのか
I just found this spirit very interesting
この精神はとても興味深いと思いました
because of this spirit
この精神のせいで
that's what i saw
それが私が見たものです
In the past biochemical experiments have been known to say
過去の生化学実験では次のようなことが知られていました。
it sends a signal
それは信号を送信します
Cell-Based
細胞ベース
Didn't know so much at the time
当時はあまり知りませんでした
but i know there's a good chance this one
でも、この可能性が高いことは分かっている
So let's go ahead and study and say
それで、先に進んで勉強して言いましょう
Is this receptor the same as we imagined
この受容体は私たちが想像していたものと同じですか
The virus stimulates receptors in its cell base
ウイルスは細胞基部の受容体を刺激します
I was very nervous and started to do this experiment.
私はとても緊張してこの実験を始めました。
Our experimental results are basically
私たちの実験結果は基本的には
this is what we want
これが私たちが望んでいることです
in a nutshell
一言で言えば
what we see here
ここで私たちが見ているもの
These English numbers TNF, RLA
これらの英語の数字 TNF、RLA
That's the name of the different cellular bases
それはさまざまな細胞基地の名前です
We found that once the virus is infected,
ウイルスが感染すると、
you find the black
あなたは黒を見つけます
After an infection
感染症の後
Although at different times
時期は違いますが
this is the hour
今はその時間です
You will find that this kind of odd number keeps going up.
このような奇数が増え続けることがわかります。
All kinds of odd numbers go up
あらゆる種類の奇数が上がります
That was before we had antibodies
抗体ができる前のことだ
We use a method called SRNA
SRNAという手法を使っています。
It is to suppress the performance of this G
このGの性能を抑えるためです
You just put this 5A and this TC3
この 5A とこの TC3 を置くだけです
hold it back
それを我慢してください
i just said
私はちょうど言いました
One of these three acceptances will catch the virus
これら 3 つの受け入れのうち 1 つがウイルスに感染します
This is the TC3
これがTC3です
but it doesn't send a signal
しかし信号は送信されません
the other one
別のもの
This is what we want to study the experimental group
これが実験グループが研究したいことです
you found out
あなたは知った
When we take this 5A performance
この5Aの性能を取ると
when suppressed like this
このように抑えられると
It would have produced this CyroCAN
この CyroCAN が生成されるはずです
just found it all down
すべてを見つけたばかりです
decline
却下
wow very happy
素敵な
it all falls
それはすべて落ちる
But this is not the point
しかし、これは重要ではありません
if it all falls
すべてが落ちたら
no discount again
再び割引はありません
how is it different from before
以前とどう違いますか
We're most excited to see this
私たちはこれを見るのがとても楽しみです
the one on the right
右側のもの
This is Inferon
これがインフェロンです
interferon
インターフェロン
you found out
あなたは知った
after you drop it
落とした後
Well, interferon does not affect
まあ、インターフェロンは影響しない
wow that day i probably
うわー、あの日私はおそらく
After spending so much money on this
これに多額のお金を費やした後、
the happiest day
最も幸せな日
just do this experiment
この実験だけをしてください
Probably just to show
おそらくただ見せるためだけ
what we did
我々のしたこと
find this receptor
この受容体を見つけてください
It only controls its inflammatory response
炎症反応のみを制御します
production of sex hormones
性ホルモンの生成
But this receptor it doesn't control interferon
しかし、この受容体はインターフェロンを制御しません
So this is a receptor for the meditative
つまり、これは瞑想的なものの受容体です
finally come true
ついに叶う
then we were thinking
それから私たちは考えていました
So is there any way to find this?
それで、これを見つける方法はありますか？
to prove that it really matters in the body
それが体にとって本当に重要であることを証明するために
Then we need to prove the effect in the body
次に、体内での効果を証明する必要があります
Of course basically we need an antibody
もちろん基本的には抗体が必要です
Because of the antibody everyone knows
誰もが知っている抗体のせいで
Antibodies can be used to treat many diseases
抗体は多くの病気の治療に使用できます
treatment-resistant cancer
治療抵抗性のがん
There are also many people who are suitable for every subject
あらゆる科目に適した人もたくさんいます
They are using Amber
彼らは琥珀を使用しています
It's because you used to have a lot of pain from the sealed wet joints.
それはあなたが濡れた関節を密閉してひどい痛みを抱えていたからです
I used to be too pure
昔は純粋すぎた
Now take an antibody and it will be cured
抗体を摂取すれば治ります
So antibodies are a very important
したがって、抗体は非常に重要です
That antibody is basically in the body
その抗体は基本的に体内にあります
We all know that there are many antibodies
抗体がたくさんあることは誰もが知っています
Our body has many cells
私たちの体にはたくさんの細胞があります
have a lot of antibodies
抗体をたくさん持っている
so science in the past
だから過去の科学
they just know
彼らはただ知っているだけです
Suppose I produce an antibody today
今日抗体を作ったとします。
After the antibody hits the body
抗体が体に入った後
I follow my standard U
私は自分の標準的な U に従います
Like here it is marked with TNF
ここのようにTNFとマークされています
or cell wipe
またはセルワイプ
When a target antibody is knocked down
標的の抗体がノックダウンされると
it can cure it
それはそれを治すことができます
But antibodies, although they are so useful
しかし、抗体はとても便利ですが、
But it's hard to make
でも作るのは大変です
because our internal
なぜなら私たちの内部では
PC packs so much
PCにはたくさんの荷物が詰め込まれています
Each PC bag produces different antibodies
各 PC バッグは異なる抗体を生成します
then you have a challenge
それならあなたには挑戦があります
If you take this particular PC bag out of your body
このPCバッグを体から取り出すと
and find out that the antibody it made is exactly what we want
そして、それが作った抗体がまさに私たちが望むものであることがわかります
and then be able to generate
そして生成できるようになります
This is a difficult
これは難しいです
so we would like to thank you very much
とても感謝しています
an important technology
重要な技術
This is called fusion flow cell fusion flow
これをフュージョンフローセルフュージョンフローといいます。
That was discovered by three scientists
それは3人の科学者によって発見されました
This is Drin
ドリンです
This Color and Mustain
このカラーとムステイン
They all got Norbert to talk
彼らは皆、ノーバートに話をさせた
Norbert speaking in 1980
1980年Norbert講
that they figured out a way
彼らはある方法を見つけたと
Because our PC bag
なぜならうちのPCバッグは
Basically though it will do antibodies
基本的には抗体を作りますが
but the cells die
しかし細胞は死んでしまう
What's the only way to keep it from dying?
それを死なせない唯一の方法は何ですか？
turn it into a cancer cell
それをガン細胞に変える
cancer cells won't die
がん細胞は死なない
So inventing a fusion flow technology
そこでフュージョンフロー技術を発明
It combines this PC bag with cancer cells
このPCバッグとガン細胞を結合させます
That's a really interesting idea
それは本当に興味深いアイデアですね
the cell will not die
細胞は死なない
won't die
死なない
it's going into some complicated way to pick it out
それを見つけるには複雑な方法が必要です
Pick out a B cell that has been making antibodies
抗体を作っているB細胞を選び出す
but won't die
でも死なない
So we can disassemble and select from this different neutralization flow
したがって、このさまざまな中和フローを分解して選択できるようになります。
we want antibodies
私たちは抗体が欲しいのです
We will use this technology to start making antibodies
この技術を使って抗体の作成を開始します
So when my students hear the teacher say
だから、生徒たちが先生の言うことを聞くと、
When he is asked to go for antibody therapy again
再び抗体療法を受けるように言われたとき
I use students to color
生徒たちを使って色を塗っています
Instantly went from happy to depressed
幸せな気持ちから一瞬にして憂鬱な気持ちになった
It's been so long
お久しぶりですね
more than two years
2年以上
two or three years
2、3年
and now make antibodies
そして今抗体を作っています
Teacher, tell me how long I will do it
先生、いつまでやるのか教えてください
So the student immediately the excitement
それで学生はすぐに興奮しました
gone soon
すぐになくなった
Just go back and start working hard to make antibodies
戻って抗体を作るために一生懸命働き始めてください
Then we disassemble and select the antibody we want
次に、必要な抗体を分解します
Three years after the antibody came, it was another big day
抗体ができてから 3 年、また大きな一日となりました
is it useful
役に立ちますか
So our student is basically
つまり、私たちの生徒は基本的に
He took the five-digit antibody we wanted
彼は我々が望んでいた5桁の抗体を取得した
Hit the rat alive and immunize him
ネズミを生きたまま殴り、免疫を与える
After immunization, he developed antibodies
予防接種後、抗体ができた
After producing antibodies, he produced a lot of B cells
抗体を作った後、B細胞を大量に作った
After the B cell, he fuses it with the swollen cell
B細胞の後、彼はそれを腫れた細胞と融合させます
Then use a drug screen to screen
次に、薬物スクリーニングを使用してスクリーニングします。
It's easy to say anyway
とにかく言うのは簡単です
It takes about a year to talk in one minute, and that's it.
1分で話すのに1年くらいかかる、それだけです。
So we worked for a long time and finally got several antibodies
そこで私たちは長い間研究し、最終的にいくつかの抗体を取得しました
What about when the antibody comes?
抗体が出来たらどうなるの？
We hit the rats
私たちはネズミを殴る
Then we use a mouse model
次に、マウスモデルを使用します
When the mouse basically hits in, you will find
マウスが基本的に入力されると、次のことがわかります。
he will bleed
彼は血を流すだろう
so put the mouse behind you see
マウスを後ろに置いてください
That's a lot of bleeding
すごい出血ですね
The intestines are also bleeding
腸からも出血してる
Then we put our production of this antibody
次に、この抗体の生産を開始します。
This is the control antibody
これはコントロール抗体です
Because doing time requires a control group
時間をかけるにはコントロールグループが必要なので
This is an antibody with no specificity
特異性のない抗体です
it is not protective
それは保護的ではありません
This is one of our antibodies
これは私たちの抗体の 1 つです
You'll find typing this
これを入力するとわかります
His subcutaneous bleeding has been suppressed.
皮下出血は抑えられている。
Intestinal bleeding was also suppressed
腸管出血も抑えられた
What about re-entry proof?
再入国証明はどうなるの？
we'll just do a dye
染料を塗るだけです
That's called Even Blue
それはイーブンブルーと呼ばれます
Because of this blue dye
この青い染料のせいで
It usually does not increase in vascular access
通常、血管アクセスは増加しません
it's inside a blood vessel
それは血管の中です
But once the pronunciation reacts
でも発音が反応すると
Its vascular access is increased
血管へのアクセスが増加します
After the increase, it will run outside and go out
増えた後は外を走って出かけます
So you start from the shade of its color
だから、その色の色合いから始めます
you can tell
教えてもいいよ
changes in its vascular access
血管アクセスの変化
Is it suppressed
抑制されているのか
This is an easy experiment to do
これは簡単にできる実験です
recently discovered
最近発見された
This is the antibody of the control group
これは対照群の抗体です
or do not fight are blue blue
あるいは戦わないとブルーブルー
After the antibody, you will find that it is not blue anymore
抗体ができたら、もう青くないことがわかります。
Then in this liver
それからこの肝臓では
Basically processing is inhibited in the gastrointestinal tract
基本的に消化管内での処理が阻害される
OK, what about after the fight?
さて、戦いの後はどうですか？
Review was not satisfied when this submission was made
この送信時にはレビューが満足されませんでした
He said, are your antibodies so good?
彼は、「あなたの抗体はそんなに大丈夫ですか？」と言いました。
Just like the Amber we just talked about
先ほど話した琥珀のように
bad food diet
悪い食事療法
that drug to compare
比較するその薬
This antibody sells about 10 B chains a year
この抗体は年間約 10 B 鎖を販売します
There are 10 B chains in the world
世界には10のBチェーンがあります
U.S. dollars are 10 billion U.S. dollars
米ドルは100億米ドルです
This is a very big medicine
これはとても大きな薬です
Let's compare and see if its blue rendering is suppressed
比較して、青色のレンダリングが抑制されているかどうかを確認してみましょう
Then you are on the right hand side with this green is under control
そうすればあなたは右側にいて、このグリーンはコントロール下にあります
You just find out and say wow it's infected and it's very blue
あなたはただそれを見つけて、感染していてとても青いと言うだけです
Then we hit the antibody, the ambo, the ambo
それから私たちは抗体、アンボ、アンボを打ちます
There is some effect, but it is not very obvious, just purple
多少の効果はありますが、あまり目立たず、ただ紫色になっているだけです
But after taking our antibody, you will find
しかし、私たちの抗体を摂取した後は、
It's red to see it's all suppressed
全てが抑制されているのを見ると真っ赤になる
So from this quantitative experiment you can clearly
したがって、この定量的実験から、明らかに次のことがわかります。
It can be known that if the antibody is knocked down, it can indeed kill it.
抗体がノックダウンされれば、実際に抗体を殺すことができることが知られています。
Vascular permeability Inhibited
血管透過性の阻害
Then let's look at its survival rate
次に生存率を見てみましょう
This is an early experiment, after doing this experiment
これは、この実験を行った後の初期の実験です
You find that no treatment or control treatment
治療法も対照治療法も存在しないことが判明した場合
The rats all died within two weeks
ラットはすべて2週間以内に死亡した
But we hit one of the antibodies
しかし、私たちは抗体の 1 つをヒットしました
Works well, about 50% of the mice don't die.
うまく機能し、マウスの約50％は死ななかった。
So doing this experiment is finally a success
ということで、この実験はついに成功です
My student finally said, teacher, are you satisfied now?
私の生徒はついにこう言いました、先生、もう満足ですか？
I can graduate, okay?
卒業できるよ、大丈夫？
Not yet, why, because I haven't cheated yet
まだ、なぜですか? まだ浮気をしていないからです。
So we later wanted to say that this study was good.
それで私たちは後でこの研究は良かったと言いたいと思いました。
Let's go and submit to a journal called Nature
Nature という雑誌に投稿しに行きましょう
This nature journal is considered to be currently in the Holy Literature
この自然誌は現在神聖文献に含まれていると考えられています
It's a top-notch magazine, so let's try it out.
一流の雑誌なのでぜひ読んでみてください。
After they voted in, they thought our stuff was very interesting.
投票した後、彼らは私たちの作品が非常に興味深いものであると考えました。
so quickly accepted
とても早く受け入れられました
after accepting
受け入れた後
Let's make a picture like this
こんな絵を作ってみましょう
Let's summarise what we found
わかったことをまとめてみましょう
That was basically in 2008
それは基本的に2008年のことでした
We will submit to this research journal
この研究誌に投稿します
You just draw a picture to explain the concept
コンセプトを説明するために絵を描くだけです
Which means we found something in mice
つまり、マウスから何かを発見したということです
normal infection time
通常の感染時間
you will generate a lot of this
あなたはこれをたくさん生成します
The so-called Trigger Addiction Base is on the left hand side.
いわゆるトリガーアディクションベースが左側にあります。
Then you increase the permeability of Chen Qius tube
次に、Chen Qiu のチューブの透過性を高めます。
After the permeability is increased, the mice will eventually die.
透過性が増加すると、マウスは最終的に死にます。
After we fight this resistance, it basically suppresses the virus
この抵抗力と戦った後、基本的にウイルスは抑制されます
it stimulates this receptor
この受容体を刺激します
So it's still a bit of a fix it's already reacting
まだ少し修正中ですが、すでに反応しています
But this amount is not high
でもこの金額は高くない
But the hepatic derivative is not affected
しかし、肝臓誘導体は影響を受けません
so it's blood vessel angiovirus
それは血管アンジオウイルスです
So in this way, we proved that the last immunity of this mouse
このようにして、このマウスの最後の免疫が証明されました。
Although this mouse received treatment
このマウスは治療を受けましたが、
He will eventually develop antibodies
最終的には抗体ができるだろう
His Tc activation does not affect the subsequent immune response at all
彼の Tc 活性化はその後の免疫反応にまったく影響を与えません
So the mouse will survive
それでネズミは生き残るだろう
so this is our job
だからこれが私たちの仕事です
Then another interesting thing happened when this was submitted
そして、これが提出されたときに、別の興味深いことが起こりました
when we were submitting
私たちが提出していたとき
Basically, this magazine has a bit of news
基本的に、この雑誌にはちょっとしたニュースがあります
So he always said that it is not allowed to publish without our permission
だから彼はいつも私たちの許可なしに出版することは許可されていないと言っていた
Because you retracted your paper after you published it
論文を出版した後に撤回したため
Wow everyone is serious
うわーみんな真剣だよ
After working for so long, the manuscript was withdrawn next to each other
あまりにも長い間作業した後、原稿は隣り合って撤回されました
the result is very tense
結果は非常に緊張しています
But one day I got a call
しかしある日電話がかかってきました
just say i'm a so and so newspaper
私はまあまあの新聞社だとだけ言ってください
The British newspaper said that I want to interview you
イギリスの新聞があなたにインタビューしたいと言いました
I was shocked when I heard that, and I said how do you know
それを聞いて私はショックを受けて、どうして分かるのかと言いました
I said I can't tell you
君には言えないって言ったよ
What should I do if my manuscript is withdrawn after I told you?
私があなたに伝えた後に私の原稿が取り下げられたらどうすればよいですか？
He said it doesn't matter, we are going to advertise for you
彼は、それは問題ではない、私たちはあなたのために宣伝するつもりだと言いました
so i just
だから私はただ
I'll tell him a little later
少し後で彼に伝えます
I didn't expect that he really advertised for me.
彼が本当に私のために広告を出してくれるとは思いませんでした。
he advertises
彼は宣伝します
this ad
この広告
not too small
小さくない
call me that
そう呼んでください
it's a british newspaper
それはイギリスの新聞です
called Telegram
テレグラムと呼ばれる
He helped us board a
彼は私たちが飛行機に乗るのを手伝ってくれた
a discovery
発見
say this
これ言ってみて
A Breakthrough
画期的な進歩
doing dengue treatment
デング熱の治療を行っている
Is Breakthrough
画期的です
so here's his report
これが彼のレポートです
Ah, is this English?
ああ、これは英語ですか？
of course i understand
もちろんわかります
Can you understand this?
これは理解できますか？
this he can see berlin
これで彼にはベルリンが見える
take a look here
ここを見てください
more like german newspapers
ドイツの新聞に近い
Then how do I know he reported me?
では、彼が私を報告したことをどうやって知ることができるのでしょうか?
Because only dengue
デング熱だけだから
He sees series 5A
彼はシリーズ 5A を見ます
i was thinking
私が考えていた
This should be reporting something to me
これは私に何かを報告しているはずです
So which of my classmates see
それで、私のクラスメートの誰が見ますか
he said nothing wrong
彼は何も間違ったことは言っていない
this is reporting your news
これはあなたのニュースを報告しています
this is a german newspaper
これはドイツの新聞です
this is AFP
これはAFPです
of course
もちろん
we understand
私たちは理解しています
Do you guys understand?
皆さん、分かりますか？
what text is this
これは何のテキストですか
It is said that this is a bilingual
バイリンガルだそうです
I also can not understand
私も理解できません
But all I see is this
でも私に見えるのはこれだけ
I'll come back to know that I'm reporting our news
私たちのニュースを報告していることを知るために戻ってきます
probably not wrong
おそらく間違ってはいない
So Russian newspapers report
そこでロシアの新聞が報じた
People's Daily
人民日報
Eating our tofu is said to be a Taiwanese scientist
私たちの豆腐を食べると台湾の科学者になると言われています
OK People's Daily also reported
OK人民日報も報じた
Then what is this text
では、この文章は何でしょうか
This seems to be from Central and South America
中南米産らしいです
basically like spanish
基本的にスペイン語と同じ
basically the same report
基本的に同じレポート
and this
この
This doesn't seem to be the case
これはそうではないようです
It is said that it seems to be Thai
タイらしいと言われています
I don't understand the same
私も同じように理解できません
But I just look at the keywords
でもキーワードだけ見てる
this dengue fever
このデング熱
Sidereal look
恒星風の外観
Nature No A
Nature 無A
I'm probably saying I'm probably not wrong
おそらく間違っていないと言っているのでしょう
Finally, it seems to be in Vietnamese
ついにベトナム語になったようです
also do the same thing
も同じことをする
so what
だから何
basically this is a story
基本的にこれは物語です
that is one of us
それは私たちの一人です
from a very simple idea
非常に単純なアイデアから
just one stimulated by reflection
反省によって刺激されたものだけ
then we start
それから始めましょう
Let's think about it, after thinking about it
考えてから考えましょう
Let's think about someone from the past
昔の人のことを考えてみましょう
a question never thought of
考えたこともなかった質問
then we get rid of it
それからそれを取り除きます
later
後で
So this is one that makes us feel
これは私たちに感じさせるものです
Doing scientific research this is probably
科学的研究を行っていると、おそらくこれは
feel most encouraged
最も励まされると感じる
It means you have an idea in Chinese
中国語でアイデアがあるという意味です
You are not bored come true you bored wish come true
あなたは退屈ではありません、それが叶います、あなたは退屈な願いが叶います
prove what you think
自分の考えを証明する
Well, after we have that experiment
さて、その実験が終わったら
Next I'm going to add a little more
次はもう少し追加していきます
People will say you're just treating dengue fever
人々はあなたがただデング熱を治療しているだけだと言うでしょう
there are so many viruses
ウイルスがたくさんあります
what's the use
使用は何ですか
Are you real?
本物ですか？
So then we're at Yellow Paper Virus
それではイエローペーパーウイルスの話です
We also made two viruses
ウイルスも2つ作りました
A virus that makes Japanese old people
日本人を老人にするウイルス
Basically also get similar results
基本的に同様の結果が得られます
Then we also make a New Nile virus
次に、新しいナイルウイルスも作成します
did a basically similar result
基本的に同様の結果が得られました
after that
その後
Another problem is
もう一つの問題は
need some imagination
想像力が必要です
Is it really only effective against dengue virus
本当にデングウイルスにしか効果がないのか
Does it have a similar effect on other viruses?
他のウイルスにも同様の影響があるのでしょうか？
then i have a good partner
それなら私には良いパートナーがいます
It's Dr. Yan Huilin at the University of Hong Kong
香港大学のヤン・フイリン博士です
Because of Hong Kong's love flu, they are doing this special movie Fu En Za
香港の愛のインフルエンザのために、彼らはこの特別な映画「Fu En Za」をやっています
Yingfu Enza This influenza virus is harmful to humans
英福円座 このインフルエンザウイルスは人体に有害です
Indecent to dengue virus
デング熱ウイルスに卑劣
You see he is very complex, he has many types
彼はとても複雑で、たくさんのタイプがあることが分かります
He has H and N H has type 18 N has type 11
彼は H と N を持っています H はタイプ 18 です N はタイプ 11 を持っています
He is also a virus and then mutation
彼もまたウイルスであり、そして突然変異である
After his mutation changes, many of his drugs are of course ineffective
彼の突然変異が変化した後、彼の薬の多くは当然無効になります
So we were thinking
それで私たちは考えていました
We can use a similar concept for such virus blessing
このようなウイルスの祝福にも同様の概念を使用できます
Wouldn't it work for us to suppress his vocal response?
彼の声の反応を抑えることはうまくいかないでしょうか？
So we picked that H5N1 to do
そこで私たちは H5N1 を選択しました。
His danger to humans you can see from this table
この表からわかる、人間に対する彼の危険性
During the two years from 1989 to 1990
1989年から1990年の2年間
When H2N2 infected this Russian food
H2N2がこのロシア料理に感染したとき
1 million deaths
死者数100万人
The most famous one from 1988 to 1999 is the H1N1
1988 年から 1999 年にかけて最も有名なものは H1N1 です。
The most serious death in history is about 50 to 100 million
史上最も深刻な死者は約5000万人から1億人
this is a very scary number
これは非常に恐ろしい数字です
Also in the early 20th century
同じく20世紀初頭
about 100 years ago
約100年前
Are we 2018 this year
今年は2018年ですか
that 100 years ago
100年前のこと
it's scary
それは怖い
This million seven trillion yeah
この100万7兆はええ
50 to 100 million deaths
死者数5,000万人から1億人
that's an incredible number
それは信じられないほどの数字です
In another H1 virus
別のH1ウイルスでは
There are also about two million in H2N2
H2N2にも約200万人いる
Then Hong Kong is about a million
それから香港は約100万人です
So now I'm probably scared
だから今、私はおそらく怖いのです
in case there is one
ある場合に備えて
What should I do if another very powerful virus comes out suddenly?
別の非常に強力なウイルスが突然現れたらどうすればよいでしょうか?
That's why we did this experiment
だからこそ私たちはこの実験を行ったのです
We'll get a genetically engineered virus
遺伝子操作されたウイルスが手に入る
This is from the University of Hong Kong
こちらは香港大学の出身です
It can be operated in P2S1 time
P2S1時でも運用可能
This is called H5N1
これはH5N1と呼ばれます
That's the first thing we say
それが私たちが最初に言うことです
Will it follow a lot
たくさん続くのかな
This Lectin combines
このレクチンが結合すると、
Then we found out that it really
その後、それが本当にあることがわかりました
Can be combined with many Lectins
多くのレクチンと組み合わせることができます
one of them
それらの中の一つ
Obviously it is this C-Lectin that sends A
明らかに、Aを送るのはこのC-レクチンです。
it will unite with it
それはそれと団結するだろう
So we'll use this grid
このグリッドを使用します
Use this H5N1 to see
このH5N1を使用して確認してください
Does blocking it work?
ブロックは機能しますか？
So basically why do this thing is the same
基本的に、なぜこれは同じなのでしょうか
Because although bird flu
なぜなら、鳥インフルエンザではあるが、
Its infection is higher on this cell than
この細胞では感染力がより高くなります。
But its main bad flu
しかし、その主な悪いインフルエンザは
It still comes from this MACOVAGE
それは今でもこのMACOVAGEから来ています
So the same thing we think is to say
つまり、私たちが考えていることと同じことが言えるのです
Although it cannot inhibit the infection of the virus
ウイルスの感染を抑えることはできませんが、
i was just about to say
ちょうど言おうとしていたところだった
When I was doing dengue virus treatment in front of me
目の前でデングウイルスの治療をしていたとき
It has a characteristic that I forgot to mention specifically, that is
具体的に言い忘れた特徴があります。
when we fight
私たちが戦うとき
In fact, the virus has not decreased
実はウイルスは減っていない
the virus is still inside
ウイルスはまだ体内に残っています
But the virus is inside
でもウイルスは体内にいる
But it won't eat our RECEPT
しかし、それは私たちのRECEPTを食べません
So it was cleared in the end
それで結局クリアできた
So we want to say yes
だから私たちはイエスと言いたいのです
Although this is not the same as dengue virus
デング熱ウイルスとは異なりますが、
Dengue virus can be found in
デング熱ウイルスは以下の場所で見つかります。
Dead cells grow a lot inside each other
死んだ細胞はお互いの中でたくさん成長します
But H1Y is mainly in this aspect compared with cell
しかし、H1Yはセルと比較して主にこの側面にあります
But it's going to make a bad flu or here
でもそれはひどいインフルエンザを引き起こすだろう
Then let's take a look at our test class
次に、テストクラスを見てみましょう
Is it still valid
まだ有効ですか
The results proved to be effective
結果は効果があることが証明されました
So that is to say
つまり、
in all the past worlds
過去のすべての世界で
in the experiment
実験で
Whether in dengue virus or
デング熱ウイルスであっても、
Or it's the same if you're emotionally ill
あるいは精神的に病んでいる場合も同様です
we are without treatment
私たちは治療を受けていません
Our cells are hyperactive
私たちの細胞は過剰に活性化しています
It generates a lot of this trigger source technology
このトリガーソーステクノロジーを大量に生成します
Then it will die is what I just said at the beginning
そうすれば死ぬだろう、というのが冒頭で言ったことだ
It will increase the pain of this blood vessel
この血管の痛みが増すでしょう
will focus on shock
ショックに焦点を当てます
Will be quadriplegic
四肢麻痺になる
then die
それから死ぬ
So if we have a good antibody
つまり、良い抗体があれば
What about after this antibody blocks it?
この抗体がそれをブロックした後はどうなるでしょうか？
Basically it is possible to make it this amount
基本的にこの金額で製作可能です
After this antibody is knocked down
この抗体がノックダウンされた後
Antibody against five
5 に対する抗体
It makes this inflammatory technique so less
この炎症技術をそれほど軽減しません
But its infectious agent still exists
しかし、その感染因子は依然として存在します
what is the benefit
メリットは何ですか
We are all
私たちは皆、
What about viral replication?
ウイルスの複製はどうなるのでしょうか？
Many of our drugs are under control
私たちの薬物の多くは管理下にあります
replication of the virus
ウイルスの複製
But sometimes when it develops resistance
しかし、時々抵抗力が現れると、
you can't heal it copy
あなたはそれを治すことはできませんコピー
Our treatment is
当院の治療は、
Whether the management virus has mutated
管理ウイルスが変異していないか
as long as you virus last
ウイルスが続く限り
It has to have limbs this
手足を通らなければなりません
If 5A is used to produce inflammatory hormones
5A が炎症性ホルモンの生成に使用される場合
I just block this part
この部分だけブロックします
no matter what virus you are
あなたがどんなウイルスであっても
Assuming your virus doesn't stimulate 5A
ウイルスが 5A を刺激しないと仮定すると
It certainly doesn't cause an inflammatory reaction
もちろん炎症反応を引き起こすことはありません
But the virus assumes it still wants
しかし、ウイルスはまだ望んでいることを想定しています
If an inflammatory response occurs through this 5A
この5Aを通じて炎症反応が起こると
I just need to block him
彼をブロックすればいいだけです
I can bring the inflammation down
炎症を抑えることができる
Finally let the body
最後に身体を任せてみましょう
his symptoms relieved
彼の症状は軽減されました
and then allow the patient to tide over
そして患者が寝返りを打てるようにする
so this is our whole
これが私たちのすべてです
A treatment for cytokine storm
サイトカインストームの治療法
a new concept
新しい概念
ok so in the end
はい、それでは最後にこれで終わりです
that is to say it is
つまりそうです
Most of this work is done at Yangming
この作業のほとんどは陽明で行われます。
My favorite mountain climbing in Yangming
私の一番好きな山登りは陽明でした
The Guanyin Mountain I see every day
毎日見るこの観音山
so this
したがって、この
I watch this every day
私はこれを毎日見ています
when doing experiments
実験をするとき
when can't do it
それができないとき
I like to climb mountains to see the scenery
私は景色を見るために山に登るのが好きです
calm yourself down
落ち着く
Especially when the experiment doesn't go well
特に実験がうまくいかないときは
Look at the mountain climbing is pretty good
見てください、登山はかなりいいです
So I suggest you come and go
だから、行ったり来たりすることをお勧めします
go to church runner
教会のランナーに行く
Finally, I would like to thank many people
最後に、たくさんの人に感謝したいと思います
Including my student Xu Cuiling in the center
私の生徒である徐翠玲を中心に
And this teacher Lin Yiling who looks like a lot
そしてこのリン・イーリン先生はよく似ています
Especially Teacher Lin Yiling
特にリン・イーリン先生
He's the one who first called me dengue virus
最初に私をデング熱ウイルスと呼んだのは彼です
He is the first humble person in Taiwan to do dengue virus
彼は台湾で初めてデング熱ウイルスを感染させた謙虚な人物だ
He taught a lot about dengue virus
彼はデング熱ウイルスについて多くのことを教えてくれました
So this is a very good cooperation between our two sides
これは両国間の非常に良い協力関係です
Then also thank our vice president, Vice President Lu, Vice President
それから私たちの副社長、ルー副社長、副社長にも感謝します。
And this Dean Wang at the beginning
そして私たちの始まりのこのディーン・ワン
This Baihui superstar gave us a support
この百恵のスーパースターが私たちをサポートしてくれました
Then my many experiments basically
それから私の多くの実験は基本的に
It was also completed in Yangming and various
陽明や諸々においても完成した。
that last love flu virus
最後の愛 インフルエンザウイルス
This was given by Dr. Yan Huining, University of Hong Kong
これは香港大学のYan Huining博士によるものです
And his boss is Paris
そして彼の上司はパリスです
Paris is a very famous professor
パリスはとても有名な教授です
He just came to Taiwan
彼は台湾に来たばかりです
He is the first to identify
彼が最初に特定した
The scientist who monitored the SARS virus
SARSウイルスを監視した科学者
So we now have a
これで、
good cooperation
良好な協力
Then use this to represent
次に、これを使用して表します
In fact, doing a research requires countless
実際、調査には数え切れないほどの作業が必要です。
In addition to countless financial and material support
数え切れないほどの財政的および物的支援に加えて、
We still need a lot of scientists
私たちはまだたくさんの科学者を必要としています
students work together
学生たちは一緒に働きます
Then there are actually a lot of discussions in the middle
それから、実際には途中でたくさんの議論があります
because of the experiment
実験のせいで
Let's talk about it now
今からそれについて話しましょう
It's easy for us to look back now
今なら振り返るのは簡単だ
Just do 1 2 3 4
1 2 3 4 を実行するだけです
In fact, when you look forward
実際、前に目を向けると、
is a lot of friction
摩擦が多いです
Then spray a lot of measures
その後、対策をたっぷりスプレーします
So this needs a lot of good friends
だからこれにはたくさんの良い友達が必要です
good partner
良いパートナー
Only by working hard can one overcome
努力することでしか乗り越えられない
To achieve what we are today
今日の私たちを達成するために
then i think it's this
それならこれだと思います
It is our best video
それは私たちの最高のビデオです
thank you
ありがとう
Li Ming
リー・ミン
Well, we thank Professor Xie Shiliang
では、謝世良教授に感謝します。
very good speech
とても良いスピーチ
And share him with us
そして彼を私たちと共有してください
this
これ
this success story
この成功物語
Then we do know that in our
そうすれば、私たちはそれを知っています
we have this
私たちはこれを持っています
Those who do scientific research are
科学研究をしている人は、
we have a very
私たちはとても持っています
is Passion
情熱です
But it is often a difficult process
しかし、それはしばしば困難なプロセスです
Then there will be some results
そうすれば何らかの結果が出てくるでしょう
These results, especially in the case of Professor Xie
これらの結果、特に謝教授の場合
In fact, the impact on society is huge
実は社会に与える影響は大きい
This is the way to treat some diseases in the future
これは将来、いくつかの病気を治療する方法です
For example, Denge is hot, other emotions are like this
例えばデンジは熱い、他の感情はこんな感じ
We just have time now for people to ask questions
今は人々が質問する時間があります
To encourage everyone, so we have the magazine Scienceman
皆さんを励ますために、私たちは雑誌『サイエンスマン』を発行しました。
If you have any questions, we will
ご質問がございましたら、
Think of this magazine as
この雑誌を次のように考えてください
as the nature of this encouragement
この励ましの性質として
Now here's one who starts
さあ、始める人がここにいます
That's it
それでおしまい
Hello teacher, this is the second time I listen to the teacher's speech
こんにちは、先生、先生の話を聞くのはこれで２回目です
I am the dermatologist at Chang Gung Hospital
私は長庚病院の皮膚科医です
The topic of the teacher's speech last time was EBV
前回の先生の講演のテーマはEBVでした
Then this time the words are
では、今回の言葉は、
I am also still very interested in viral infection
私もウイルス感染症には今でもとても興味があります
Then I have a few questions to ask the teacher
それから先生にいくつか質問したいことがあります
is the first to say
最初に言うのは
Because the Passo group is in
パッソグループが入っているので
That is to say, on our ice bed
つまり、私たちの氷床の上で
That is, many Passo groups will cause
つまり、多くのパッソグループは、
Satocon stone looks like this
サトコン石はこんな感じ
That's actually being a patient
それは実際に患者である
When a Satocon stone occurs
サトコン石が発生した場合
He's actually pretty consistent
彼は実際かなり一貫性がある
that's hard to find that says
それは見つけるのが難しいです
Accurate Passo group to treat
確確的Passo群來治療
Just come is the Antifiral group
さあ、Antifiral グループが来ます
That is to say, the patient
つまり、患者さんは、
Usually this happens
通常、これは起こります
It's just that we are just shooting birds
私たちが無差別に鳥を撃っているだけです
all antibiotics
すべての抗生物質
All antiviral drugs are like this
抗ウイルス薬はどれもこんな感じ
The first question I want to ask the teacher is
先生に最初に聞きたい質問は、
Do we currently have some cruell
私たちは今、残酷なことをしていますか？
It is the Satocon stone that can be used
使えるサトコンストーンです
The type of his Satocon
他的Satocon的type
or his proportions and performance
あるいは彼のプロポーションとパフォーマンス
pushing his Passo group back and forth
彼のパッソグループを前後に押し出す
what kind of infection
どのような感染症ですか
This is the first one
これが最初のものです
The second is that I want to ask the teacher to say
2つ目は、先生に言いたいことです。
Hit CLEC5A Antibody
打CLEC5A Antibody
Come to suppress the function of Information
情報の機能を抑制するようになる
when is better
いつが良いですか
is post infection
感染後です
Then it is also effective to fight before infection
それなら感染する前に対策するのも効果的です
It's been a long time
おひさしぶりですね
Like because honestly there are a lot of viral infections
正直ウイルス感染が多いから
Then we can't have only one infection in our lifetime
そうすれば、一生に一度しか感染しないはずがない
So if we later treated it as a preventative medicine
それで、後でそれを予防薬として扱ったら
like the gram flu
グラムインフルエンザみたいに
Will you call more times
もっと何度も電話しますか
Then it didn't work like this
その後、このようには機能しませんでした
The third question I want to know says
私が知りたい3番目の質問は次のとおりです
Because I'm doing enterovirus now
今エンテロウイルスやってるから
Then I want to know that it is the part of the enterovirus
それから、それがエンテロウイルスの一部であることを知りたいです
It is enterovirus, which is actually a part of TLR
それはエンテロウイルスであり、実際にはTLRの一部です
later a reaction
その後の反応
But the weird thing is that it happens in some places
しかし奇妙なのは、それが場所によっては起こるということです
It's the throat, the palms, the soles of the feet.
喉、手のひら、足の裏です。
Can the teacher give me some advice?
先生は私にアドバイスをいただけますか？
That is why it only looks like this in these places
だからこういうところだけこんな風に見えるんだよ
Is there any marker
マーカーはありますか
I can look for this
これなら探せますよ
Thanks
ありがとう
The first question is to say
最初の質問はこう言います
Is there any way we can contract these symptoms from it
これらの症状を軽減する方法はありますか?
Made back to what kind of virus it is
どのようなウイルスなのかを遡ってみる
In fact, this problem is a bit difficult
実はこの問題はちょっと難しいんです
because
なぜなら
you know our body
あなたは私たちの体を知っていますか
suppose today
今日だと仮定して
We have today that sequencing technology called automatic
今日、私たちは自動と呼ばれるシーケンス技術を持っています。
Next Generation Sequencing Technology
次世代シーケンス技術
You know suppose to put a person
人を置くと仮定するとわかります
After all the DNA is extracted from the whole body
やっぱり全身からDNAが抽出されるんですね
Ask your body's DNA
あなたの体のDNAに尋ねてください
It's the DNA in your 23-pair display body
それは 23 ペアのディスプレイ本体の DNA です
Approximately how much DNA is in your body
体内にある DNA の量はおよそどれくらいですか
Does this student have any idea
この学生は何か考えがありますか
Weird question, isn't it?
奇妙な質問ですね。
Shouldn't knowledge be protected? Baidu is my DNA.
知識は保護されるべきではないでしょうか? Baidu は私の DNA です。
You first look at how much of your own DNA is in your house
まず、自分の家に自分の DNA がどのくらいあるかを調べます。
According to scientists' estimates, only about 20%
科学者の推定によると、わずか約20％
what does that mean
どういう意味ですか
80% of your body
体の80％
There are many microorganic
微生物がたくさんいる
exists in your body
あなたの体の中に存在します
you have no idea who he is
あなたは彼が誰なのか分かりません
He was with you all his life
彼は生涯ずっとあなたと一緒にいました
This is what we now use to sequence
これは現在シーケンスに使用しているものです
So the answer to the question is to say
したがって、質問に対する答えは次のようになります
when we have one
私たちがそれを持っているとき
You come to pronounce the reaction especially in the hospital
特に病院では反応が顕著になる
I often spray that called
というスプレーをよくかけます。
ass earrings
お尻のイヤリング
then have a fever
それから熱が出ます
don't know anything
何も知りません
now of course
今はもちろん
Of course we have some sequencing technology to know who
もちろん、誰が誰なのかを知るためのシーケンス技術はあります。
but even if you want to know who he is
でも彼が誰なのか知りたくても
It's a long way to do treatment with you
あなたと一緒に治療を行うのは長い道のりです
That's why we do research
だからこそ私たちは研究をするのです
That is to say, what I just said
つまり、今言ったことは、
Viruses that can cause severe cell-based viruses actually have a characteristic
重篤な細胞ベースのウイルスを引き起こす可能性のあるウイルスには、実際には特徴があります
That is to say, he will stimulate MACOFIG
つまり、MACOFIGを刺激することになります。
He will stimulate MACOFIG
彼は MACOFIG を刺激します
For example, let's talk about some slower viruses
たとえば、遅いウイルスについて話しましょう。
For example, your Baxinian virus
たとえば、バクシニアウイルス
Some lots of virus or hepatitis B virus
大量のウイルスまたはB型肝炎ウイルス
Will he cause a cytomegalo storm?
彼はサイトメガロストームを引き起こすでしょうか？
he won't do so much
彼はあまりやりません
So it will cause a cytogenetic storm
それで細胞遺伝学的嵐を引き起こすだろう
Almost all will stimulate MACOFIG
ほとんどすべてが MACOFIG を刺激します
despinocytes
デスピノサイト
So you said how to treat
それであなたは治療方法を言いました
This is also the purpose of our research
これが私たちの研究の目的でもあります
We treat these 5A
この5Aを扱います
This is the first time to prove our concept that
私たちのコンセプトが証明されたのはこれが初めてです。
Our MACOFIG is
私たちのMACOFIGは
There is a receptor on it
その上に受容体があります
will detect the virus and cause an inflammatory response
ウイルスを検出して炎症反応を引き起こす
The problem is that playing 5A doesn't work either.
問題は、5A をプレイしても機能しないことです。
Of course you can think about our receptors
もちろん、私たちの受容体について考えてもいいでしょう
so many
とてもたくさんの
It is unnecessary to know all viruses
すべてのウイルスを知る必要はありません
you rely on this
あなたはこれに依存しています
Our general Kang Ben trial to participate in feel
私たちの一般的なカンベントライアルに参加するには
Why do I have so many receptors to bless him so powerfully?
なぜ私には彼をこれほど強力に祝福する受容体がたくさんあるのでしょうか？
So it must not be all
だからそれがすべてではないはずだ
So in fact, what we are studying now has been
実際、私たちが今研究しているのは、
Not just researching upstream anymore
もう上流の研究だけではない
We're now looking at the downstream messaging that says he
私たちは現在、次のようなダウンストリーム メッセージを調べています。
His message is that he is going down
彼のメッセージは彼が倒れるということだ
how is this passed down
これはどのように受け継がれているのでしょうか
Then we can find a common ground to do
そうすれば、やるべき共通点を見つけることができます
a comment target
一個comment target
Basically, there are many of us now
基本的に、今は私たちの多くがいます
The pronunciation response is basically cox 2
発音応答は基本的にcox 2です。
we all heard one
私たち全員が一つ聞いた
Conscious pronunciation response is the cox 2 inhibitor is basically like this
意識的な発音反応はcox 2阻害剤は基本的にこんな感じです
Because he often passes through this cox 2 when he pronounces
なぜなら、彼は発音するときにこのcox 2を通過することが多いからです。
So this finds the target
これでターゲットが見つかります
So we're going to cure the cell tech storm now
だから私たちは今、セルテクノロジーの嵐を治すつもりです
We've gone from the earliest days of this
私たちはこの初期の頃から去ってしまいました
Upstream, let's find out slowly
上流、ゆっくり探そう
he may have many receptors
彼は多くの受容体を持っているかもしれない
But he's going to have a vocal response at the end
でも最後には声で反応するだろう
he will be one downstream
彼は一つ下流になるだろう
consistent delivery of a message
一貫したメッセージの配信
So we're trying to find the signal for that message right now
そこで私たちは今、そのメッセージを通過させるための信号を見つけようとしています
then go terminate it
それからそれを終了しに行きます
In this way we can use a medicine
このようにして薬を使うことができるのです
like cox2
cox2のような
we do cox2 you will compare almost any reaction
cox2 を実行すると、ほぼすべての反応を比較できます
It won't hurt after you get it down
下ろしたら痛くないよ
Basically the principle is like this
基本的に原理はこんな感じ
We also hope that we can find such a target
私たちもそのようなターゲットを見つけられることを願っています
After that, no matter what kind of virus
その後は、どんなウイルスであっても
The cytokine storm everyone created
みんなが作ったサイトカインストーム
We can all use this in therapy
私たちは皆、これを治療に使用できます
Then your third question is to grow virus 71
3 番目の質問は、ウイルス 71 を増殖させることです。
I have done this too
これもやりました
long virus 71 it actually
長いウイルス 71 それは実際には
It does not affect the severe cytokine storm
重篤なサイトカインストームには影響しません
So basically this we also experimented with
基本的にこれは私たちも実験しました
it doesn't stimulate
刺激しません
subcell
サブセル
It also does not create a cytokine storm
サイトカインストームも引き起こさない
So the specific symptoms it produces are due to
したがって、それが引き起こす具体的な症状は次のようなものによるものです。
What kind of cell does the virus want to enter?
ウイルスはどのような細胞に侵入しようとしているのでしょうか？
It depends on whether there are receptors on the cell
細胞に受容体があるかどうかによって決まります
its receptor is
その受容体は
receptors that help it get into the cell
細胞内への侵入を助ける受容体
It is different from the receptors of gill translucency syndrome we talked about today
今日お話しした鰓半透明症候群の受容体とは異なります。
So because your body has a specific receptor
つまり、あなたの体には特定の受容体があるため、
So the virus will go to specific cells
つまりウイルスは特定の細胞に行きます
like hepatitis virus
肝炎ウイルスのような
he actually goes to the liver
彼は実際に肝臓に行きます
he won't go anywhere else
彼は他にはどこにも行かない
So this type of treatment basically
したがって、このタイプの治療は基本的には
It will be different from the strategy we talked about today.
今日話し合った戦略とは異なります。
So this scientific question is actually
つまり、この科学的疑問は実際には
There is no way to solve it with just one ability
一つの能力だけでは解決できない
so doing cell trends is my specialty
細胞のトレンドを調べるのが私の専門分野です
But you just mentioned longevity poison 71
でもあなたは今、長寿の毒について言及しました 71
presumably have a different strategy
おそらく別の戦略があるでしょう
For example, the most common thing is that everyone is developing vaccines.
たとえば、最も一般的なのは、誰もがワクチンを開発していることです。
For longevity poison, it is said that this clinical trial
長寿毒については、この臨床試験が行われていると言われています
seems to be ok
大丈夫のようです
Report on road seems to be all right
道路上のレポートは大丈夫のようです
So this requires a different strategy to treat
したがって、これには別の治療戦略が必要です
But the example I am talking about today is the most important
しかし、私が今日話している例は最も重要です
All are based on cell trend storm
すべてセルトレンドストームに基づいています
thank you teacher
ありがとう、先生
I want to ask
聞きたいです
Recently, it is often heard that pharmaceutical companies are developing
最近、製薬会社が開発しているとよく聞きます。
Lantern fever vaccine
ランタン熱ワクチン
It is because he has many similar blood types due to the dengue virus
デング熱ウイルスの影響で血液型が似ていることが多いためです。
But so it often happens that there is no way
しかし、どうしようもないことがよくあるので、
All types can be protected
すべてのタイプを保護できます
So the development is not so smooth
そのため開発はそれほどスムーズではありません
Then I just want to listen to Mr. Xie's speech
それなら謝さんのスピーチを聞きたいです。
This 5A
この5A
The will seems to be quite effective and quite tangible.
意志は非常に効果的で、非常に具体的であるように見えます。
That
それか
And there are antibodies
そして抗体もある
Is there any pharmaceutical company willing to go?
参加してくれる製薬会社はあるでしょうか？
to this direction
この方向へ
5A go
5A 行きます
Are you developing this drug?
この薬を開発していますか？
Thanks
ありがとう
dengue virus
デング熱ウイルス
just two questions
たった2つの質問
one is the vaccine
一つはワクチンです
because vaccines do
ワクチンがそうなるから
inside all vaccines
すべてのワクチンの中に
And every time I see manufacturers of dengue vaccines, I say you are very brave.
デング熱ワクチンの製造業者に会うたびに、私はあなたがとても勇敢だと言います。
Just pick the hardest one in the world to do
世界で一番難しいことを選んでください
because he has a different
彼には違うものがあるから
four blood types
4つの血液型
Then we all know that dengue virus infection has a special phenomenon called
デングウイルス感染には、と呼ばれる特別な現象があることは誰もが知っています。
is the antibody
抗体です
It is a phenomenon called AD
ADと呼ばれる現象です
It's your antibody
それはあなたの抗体です
As long as you can only synthesize one type
1種類しか合成できない限り
But if it cannot be combined with other types
ただし、他のタイプと組み合わせられない場合は、
that sometimes he is a disaster
彼は時々災難になることがある
when it cannot neutralize other types
他のタイプを無力化できない場合
The presence of this antibody prevents the disease from becoming more serious
この抗体の存在により、病気の重症化が防止されます。
So doing vaccines
それでワクチンをやる
it's a big challenge
それは大きな挑戦だ
how do you promise to say
どのように言うと約束しますか
Get vaccinated after entering alone
一人で入ったら予防接種を受ける
He can produce antibodies
彼は抗体を産生できる
protect everything
すべてを守る
this is a big challenge
これは大きな挑戦です
So of course it shouldn't be difficult
もちろん難しいことではありません
so as to say
言うように
Can it be used to treat diseases
病気の治療に使用できますか
i just said
私はちょうど言いました
when we published earlier
以前に公開したとき
In fact, we have authorized a manufacturer in Chinese
実際、当社は中国のメーカーを認定しています。
let's give us some more money
もっとお金をあげましょう
Then do this experiment
それからこの実験をしてください
but i just said
でも私は今言いました
when you go to therapy
セラピーに行くとき
Antibodies are basically more expensive
抗体は基本的に高価です
The other is the time you talked about
もう一つはあなたが話した時間です
Someone just asked me
誰かが私に尋ねました
when is it effective
いつ効果がありますか
all infectious diseases
すべての感染症
like you eat the gram flu
グラムインフルエンザにかかったように
The sooner you eat, the more effective
早く食べるほど効果的
Does that have a preventive effect?
あれって予防効果あるの？
With your blessing
あなたの祝福とともに
i never did
私は決してしませんでした
Bless you before you get infected
感染する前に祝福してください
After you get the antibody first
まずは抗体を取得してから
it fights again
それはまた戦う
basically it will help
基本的には役に立ちます
So who is going to buy this antibody
では、誰がこの抗体を買うのでしょうか？
I often say should
すべきだとよく言います
should be sold to the U.S. Department of Defense
米国国防総省に売却すべきだ
The United States likes to send giants to fight all over the world
米国は世界中で戦うために巨人を派遣することを好む
So it's better to get up first and then go to war
だから、まず起きてから戦争に行く方が良い
he may be asymptomatic
彼は無症状かもしれない
But after all, it is more impractical
しかし結局のところ、それはより非現実的です
Most of the sick spots are because he's already infected
病状のほとんどはすでに感染しているためです
he has symptoms
彼には症状がある
Then he started to take medicine
それから彼は薬を飲み始めました
So in practice
それで実際には
Although using antibodies to prove that we are infected
私たちが感染していることを証明するために抗体を使用しますが、
but you have to make a drug
でも薬を作らなければならない
Antibodies are not optimal
抗体が最適ではない
Because your house is not playing very early
あなたの家はあまり早くから演奏しないから
Because after many viruses are infected
多くのウイルスに感染した後だから
We know that when a virus enters the body it produces a disease called
ウイルスが体内に侵入すると、と呼ばれる病気を引き起こすことがわかっています。
called Biremia
ビレミアと呼ばれる
There is a virus all over the world
世界中にウイルスが蔓延している
But his experiment won't be very long
しかし彼の実験はそれほど長くはかからないだろう
he'll be gone in a few days
彼は数日以内にいなくなるだろう
so at this time
だからこの時点では
He welcomes the reaction while it's in progress
彼は進行中の反応を歓迎します
we did experiments
私たちは実験をしました
Suppose we play very late
とても遅くまでプレイするとします
The later you beat him, the worse the effect will be.
彼を倒すのが遅ければ遅いほど、その影響は大きくなります。
So now our new treatment target
さて、私たちの新しい治療目標は
It's that we're studying his messaging.
私たちは彼のメッセージを研究しているということです。
It just depends on which virus he drives.
それは彼がどのウイルスを駆動するかによって決まります。
Which % tax is the messaging
メッセージは何%の税金ですか
We hope to use small molecule drugs
低分子医薬品の活用を期待しています
Able to be like Costool
コスツールのようになれる
Go to Tarkey those specific molecules
それらの特定の分子をターキーに移動します
then come for treatment
それから治療に来てください
This is probably more realistic
こっちのほうが現実的かもしれない
This is what we are working on now
これが私たちが現在取り組んでいることです
JV
合弁会社
X
バツ
hello chase
こんにちは、追いかけます
i want to ask two questions
2つの質問がしたいです
the first one is you
最初の人はあなたです
The lectures on knowledge and karma are mentioned above.
知識とカルマについての講義は上記に記載されています。
In the future, this receptor may be a
将来的には、この受容体は
One of the treatments for the red wolf
レッドウルフの治療法の一つ
A New Direction for Calibration
校正の新しい方向性
can you explain it to us
説明してもらえますか
The second is to say that in fact, in your recent
2 つ目は、実際、最近の
It is on the Nature Combination
ネイチャーコンビネーションにあります
It is mentioned that
言及されているのは、
This receptor-deficient keratin in the liver
肝臓にあるこの受容体欠損ケラチン
lead to more severe inflammation
より重篤な炎症を引き起こす
can you explain it to us
説明してもらえますか
The two questions you just asked are
あなたが今尋ねた 2 つの質問は、
In our recent post that
最近の投稿では、
In the Nature Communications article
Nature Communications の記事で
What kind of function does this receptor have?
この受容体はどのような働きをするのでしょうか？
We found that this receptor basically
この受容体は基本的に
He not only knows about viruses
彼はウイルスについて知っているだけではありません
He will also know Seohyun
彼もソヒョンのことを知っているだろう
Why do this research?
なぜこの研究を行うのでしょうか?
Because if you think about it, how can our body have a society to make it?
なぜなら、考えてみると、私たちの体はどのようにして社会を形成できるのでしょうか?
Made you sick
病気になった
isn't that reasonable
それは合理的ではありませんか
So it must have some other function
したがって、他の機能があるはずです
then we're in a place where we have a chance to find out that it's actually
そして、私たちはそれが実際にそうなっていることを知るチャンスがある場所にいます。
Another cell in the body is called
体内の別の細胞は次のように呼ばれます。
Granules are tetraneutrophils
顆粒は四好中球です
English called New Show Pair
英文叫New Show Pair
It also performs very well
パフォーマンスも非常に優れています
What about this cell?
この細胞はどうなるのでしょうか？
when it is activated
活性化されると
it produces a special phenomenon
それは特殊な現象を引き起こす
will generate a structure called Nate
Nate と呼ばれる構造を生成します
is that it spits out the DNA
それはDNAを吐き出すということです
That is, after the cell expands, it will spit out the DNA
つまり、細胞が拡大した後、DNAが吐き出されます。
After spitting it out, its DNA will be sticky
吐き出すとDNAがベタベタになる
Then stick the bacteria
次にバクテリアを付着させます
After sticking bacteria
細菌が付着した後
it will keep the bacteria expanding
バクテリアが増殖し続けることになります
So the DNA issue you just mentioned is to say
つまり、あなたが今言及した DNA の問題は、つまり、
it gets very inflamed in the liver
肝臓で非常に炎症が起こる
but just say
でもただ言ってください
Suppose you get a bacterial infection
細菌感染症にかかったとします
Then when this infection
そして、この感染症が起こったとき、
If there are five of them
5人もいたら
In fact, your anti-bacterial effect will be greatly reduced
実際、抗菌効果は大幅に低下します
This is to talk about the importance of public opinion treatment
これは世論の扱いの重要性について話すためです
that is, you have to use the right
つまり、正しいものを使用する必要があります
Just like we are using this NTI-TNF to treat
私たちがこの NTI-TNF を治療に使用しているのと同じように
This cracking wind is the same as the joint point, what is the consequence?
このひび割れ風は接合点と同じですが、結果はどうなるのでしょうか？
Its price is that it causes tuberculosis
その代償として結核を引き起こすということだ
so get tuberculosis
それで結核になる
So the same, suppose in the future you want the Receptor Tarkey to do this Parsway
同様に、将来、レセプター ターキーにこのパーズウェイを実行させたいと仮定します。
You may be at risk
あなたは危険にさらされているかもしれません
Do you supercharge certain susceptibility to bacterial infections
細菌感染に対する特定の感受性を高めますか
This is to answer your second question
これは 2 番目の質問に答えるものです
Then why do you say it has something to do with the red savage wolf cabin?
では、なぜそれがレッド・サベージ・ウルフの小屋と関係があると言えるのですか？
you this is what we are doing
あなた、これが私たちがやっていることです
Because the red savage wolf cabin is basically considered to say
レッド・サベージ・ウルフ・キャビンは基本的に次のように考えられているので
It is because NUCHOFILIER that net generates too much
NUCHOFILIERがネットを生産しすぎるからです
So we actually did some experiments
そこで実際にいくつかの実験をしてみました
is when it has too much net
それはネットが多すぎるときです
It is true that these five bits are a very important factor to control the net structure generated by NUCHOFILIER
確かに、これらの 5 ビットは、NUCHOFILIER によって生成されるネット構造を制御するための非常に重要な要素です。
So ours is a discussion
つまり、私たちの議論は議論です
If the overproduction of this net is related to 5A
このネットの過剰生産が 5A に関連している場合
In the future, it is possible for us to use the 5A of consciousness
将来的には意識の5Aを活用できるようになる
To be aware that this net produces
このネットが生み出すものに注意してください
Then go to realize the sex sac growth of red ants
それから赤アリの性嚢の成長を実感してください
This is of course a long-term inference.
もちろん、これは長期的な推論です。
basically like this
基本的にこのように
thank you thank you for your question
ありがとう、ご質問ありがとうございます
The first question is also closed on the pre-influenza
インフルエンザ前に関する最初の質問も終了しました
This is indeed what we have considered
これはまさに私たちが検討したことです
Its importance in the future of influenza viruses
インフルエンザウイルスの将来におけるその重要性
Because of dengue virus it can't have
デングウイルスのせいでそれはできない
The Importance of the Influenza Virus
インフルエンザウイルスの重要性
So we in this question
したがって、この質問では
we are in this problem
私たちはこの問題の中にいます
Because dengue virus it after all the vast majority of people
なぜならデング熱ウイルスは結局のところ大多数の人が感染するからです
In fact, dengue virus is actually the vast majority of people
実際、デング熱ウイルスは実際には大多数の人々に感染しています。
Its symptoms are not obvious
その症状は明らかではありません
it really gets serious
それは本当に深刻になります
only about 10%
わずか10％程度
There will be more serious symptoms
さらに深刻な症状が出てくる
And most of them are in Taiwan
そしてそのほとんどが台湾にいます
Older, less resistant
古いほど耐性が低い
But the flu virus is different
しかし、インフルエンザウイルスは違います
flu virus your symptoms
インフルエンザウイルスの症状
when you are infected
感染したとき
Especially the one that reacts very strongly sometimes
特に時々非常に強く反応するもの
so this is really serious
これは本当に深刻です
So we use the flu virus
そこでインフルエンザウイルスを使うのです
Basically the idea is
基本的にその考えは
You just said you didn't do it
やってないって言っただけだよ
Because dengue virus has only four lines
デング熱ウイルスには4行しかないため
That flu virus has so many lines
あのインフルエンザウイルスにはたくさんの線がある
So let's say we have a flu virus
それでは、インフルエンザウイルスがあるとします。
You can also find a common pathway
共通の経路を見つけることもできます
Is it possible to realize the western foundation caused by influenza virus
インフルエンザウイルスによる欧米の基盤は実現できるのか
it's really what we think
それは本当に私たちが考えていることです
so we have been doing
それで私たちはやっています
So our treatment method is basically
そこで当院の治療方法は基本的には
When I came up with this idea
このアイデアを思いついたとき
In fact, it subverts the general idea
実際、それは一般的な概念を覆します
Because normally we treat viral infections
通常はウイルス感染症の治療を行っているため、
The first thought is whether there is a drug
最初に考えられるのは薬があるかどうかです
able to realize it replicates
複製されることを認識できる
it won't copy
それはコピーされません
it won't have disease
病気にはならないだろう
But why something like this
しかし、なぜこのようなことが
challenged for some reason
何らかの理由で挑戦されました
It's because the virus mutates sometimes
ウイルスは時々変異するから
it will not be healed
治らないだろう
Another reason is that
もう一つの理由は、
that virus hypothetical
そのウイルスは仮説です
when it has entered the body
体内に入ったとき
elicit a vocal response
声による反応を引き出す
You are healing the replication and it is too late
レプリケーションを修復中ですが、もう手遅れです
it's been a lot
たくさんありました
so you just said you didn't say
だからあなたは言っていないと言ったばかりです
we make this drug
私たちはこの薬を作っています
Another purpose of doing this research
この研究を行うもう一つの目的
really hope to find a virus after infection
感染後にウイルスが見つかることを本当に願っています
inside the macroscopic cells
巨視的な細胞の内部
A common path that elicits an articulatory response
調音反応を引き出す共通の経路
Find a cure from hope
希望から治療法を見つける
is so
そうだね
Then you obviously know my details.
そうすれば、あなたは明らかに私の詳細を知っています。
you also know i do this
あなたも私がこれをしていることを知っています
There is nothing wrong with K-Z's treatment
K-Zの治療には何の問題もありません
I actually did this first
実はこれを最初にやったんです
Doing the radiation tumor treatment in various ways
さまざまな方法で放射線腫瘍治療を行う
For cancer, you use a lot
がんの場合はたくさん使います
Institute of Cancer Drugs
がん治療薬研究所
After treatment, there will indeed be more immune responses
治療後は確かに免疫反応が増加します
including some that can cause allergic reactions
アレルギー反応を引き起こす可能性のあるものを含む
some just cause that skin
その肌の原因となるものもあります
It will itch and hurt
痒くて痛くなるよ
This base rotation is actually quite interesting
このベースローテーションは実に興味深いです
But I haven't researched this field yet
しかし、私はまだこの分野を調べていません
but i believe
でも私は信じます
All of these things are what I'm talking about today
これらすべてが今日私が話していることです
The circle in the first picture is related
最初の写真の丸が関係しています
Because no matter what kind of disease
だってどんな病気でも
almost always
ほとんどいつも
it elicits a vocal response
声による反応を引き出す
It must be stimulating our body
きっと身体に刺激を与えているのでしょうね
a certain partsway
とある途中
caused by a receptor
受容体によって引き起こされる
so bless says
そう祝福は言う
Someone is particularly interested in this
誰かがこれに特に興味を持っています
He might be able to use something like
彼は次のようなものを使用できるかもしれません
go find out
調べに行く
After chemotherapy or various medications that we do
化学療法や当院で行われるさまざまな薬物療法の後
what element does it produce
それはどのような要素を生み出すのか
what kind of receptors to stimulate
どのような受容体を刺激するか
Then I believe there is still a lot to be done.
それから、やるべきことはまだたくさんあると思います。
is possible to find a way to suppress its inflammatory response
炎症反応を抑制する方法を見つけることが可能です
Hello
こんにちは
I want to ask about this 5A receptor
この5A受容体について聞きたいのですが
It is mainly through which transfer molecule
それは主にどの分子を介して移動しますか
to open the downstream bacteria
下流の細菌を開く
And I saw a slide
そしてスライドを見ました
It's written that it activates this NLRP3, the inflammatory payload
このNLRP3、炎症性ペイロードを活性化すると書かれています。
Then it is through increasing the protein of this load body
次に、このロードボディのタンパク質を増やすことによって行われます
or increase its aggregation
またはその集計を増やす
Then there is another
それから、もう一つあります
For this feeling you have about this and that Cyrolyte Dome
あれやこれやのサイロライトドームに対するこの感情について
That is to say, it actually said at the beginning
つまり、実は冒頭でも言っていたのですが、
It will first initiate some of the more important Cyrokyne
それは最初に、より重要な Cyrokyne のいくつかを開始します。
and then cause the entire
そして全体の原因となる
Or is it that he turned on the entire Path bit from the beginning?
それとも最初から Path ビット全体をオンにしたのでしょうか?
Then all the track cards come out
その後、すべてのトラックカードが出てきます
that's a very good question
それはとても良い質問です
That's what we've been doing lately
それが私たちが最近やっていることです
That is, since we discovered that many viruses can stimulate 5A
つまり、多くのウイルスが 5A を刺激できることが判明して以来、
We are very interested in his next entry
私たちは彼の次のエントリーに非常に興味があります
How is the entry of interest passed on?
関心のあるエントリはどのように引き継がれますか?
So the first research we did was to do this inflamed body
そこで私たちが行った最初の研究は、この炎症を起こした体を調査することでした
Because inflammation is now a very important Path bit
炎症は現在非常に重要なパスビットであるため
they have a fever together
彼らは一緒に熱を持っています
Denge Fever is actually called Denge Fever
デンジフィーバーは実際にはデンジフィーバーと呼ばれます
It is because when this patient is infected
なぜなら、この患者が感染した場合には、
He develops a very bad temperature and a high fever
彼は非常にひどい体温と高熱を出しました
So we were wondering
そこで私たちは疑問に思いました
Then why does it cause this fever
ではなぜこのような発熱が起こるのでしょうか
It proves that this path is also taken
この道も通ったことが証明される
Because he has the ability to activate the inflammatory body
炎症を起こす身体を活性化する能力があるため、
Then will he have any other paths?
では、彼には他の道があるだろうか？
this is what we are doing now
これが私たちが今やっていることです
Because few people did 5A research in the past
過去に5Aの研究をした人がほとんどいなかったため
Because I don't know who is on him
誰が彼に関わっているのか分からないから
Then do this kind of pronunciation response. Many people have studied this message transmission in the past.
そして、このような発音応答を行うという、このメッセージ伝達については、これまでに多くの人が研究してきました。
They are all lions, this lion is provocative and eats you know
彼らは皆ライオンです、このライオンは挑発的で、ご存知のように食べます
Because they don't like to be a giant cell
彼らは巨大細胞になることを好まないからです
What I want to say is that it is very hard for us to do this kind of research
私が言いたいのは、この種の研究を行うのは非常に難しいということです
We're all going to use mouse cells or human blood cells
私たちは皆、マウスの細胞か人間の血液細胞を使用するつもりです
The reason is because many people are researchers and I also want to use cell pigs
理由は研究者が多く、私も細胞豚を使いたいからです。
Doing Cell Pigs vs. People Doing Research
細胞豚と研究者
good people who do cancer research
がんの研究をする良い人たち
Because cancer is cells that are absent
がんは存在しない細胞だから
So a lot of the results with Cellpigs are pretty good
Cellpigs の結果の多くは非常に良好です
we have to react
私たちは反応しなければなりません
We bless with a cell pig
私たちは細胞豚を祝福します
when infected with a virus
ウイルスに感染したとき
It will react like our mouse
私たちのマウスのように反応します
Cellular reaction with human blood
人間の血液との細胞反応
totally different
全く違います
So it's really hard for us to do this experiment.
したがって、この実験を行うのは非常に困難です。
So the questions you just mentioned
それで、あなたが今挙げた質問は、
What is its downstream
その下流は何ですか
We now probably know that it is downstream through SYK
おそらく、それが SYK を介して下流にあることがわかります。
Then after passing through the downstream, you will eat a Buddha chair
そして下流を抜けたら仏陀椅子を食べます
buddhist tree
仏教の木
But there is a big gap in the middle
でも真ん中に大きな隙間がある
we don't know
私たちは知りません
This is the direction of our current research
これが私たちの現在の研究の方向性です
This is back to what I just said
これは先ほどの話に戻りますが、
the path of this study
この研究の道のり
This study is actually a continuation of the work
この研究は実際には研究の続きです
is endless
終わりがない
We are now hoping that before I retire
私たちは今、引退する前にそれを望んでいます
To be able to figure out the dirty path
ダーティパスを把握できるようにする
Then come again maybe I'll have a chance to be here next time
それからまた来てください、次回はここに来る機会があるかもしれません
share my work with you
私の作品をあなたと共有してください
and then be able to give you more clarity
そうすれば、より明確に理解できるようになります
A more satisfactory answer would be this
より満足のいく答えはこれです
Thanks
ありがとう
Any question
ご質問は何でも
ok, may I ask the lady
わかりました、女性に聞いてもいいですか
thank you
ありがとう
Because I was late just now and there was a miss in front of me
さっき遅刻して目の前にミスがあったから
so you might mention
それであなたは言及するかもしれません
maybe i didn't hear you clearly
あなたの声がはっきり聞こえなかったかもしれません
As for the cause of the inflammation you just mentioned
先ほどおっしゃった炎症の原因についてですが、
some of them are viruses
そのうちのいくつかはウイルスです
One of them mentioned is that
その中の一つとして挙げられているのが、
What about urea crystallization?
尿素の結晶化はどうですか？
i want to understand
理解したいです
Normally, our urea will crystallize, that's right.
通常、尿素は結晶化します。
But what is causing it to over crystallize?
しかし、何が過剰結晶化を引き起こしているのでしょうか？
can understand
理解することができます
Thanks
ありがとう
Crystallization is of course the first
もちろん結晶化が最初です
The basic reason is because it
基本的な理由は、
it's high
高いです
because it's as high as a
と同じくらい高いので
Worse than that spiritual point
精神世界よりひどい
you call it crystallization
あなたはそれを結晶化と呼びます
But crystallization occurs in the body
しかし体内では結晶化が起こる
there are many factors
多くの要因があります
such as blood circulation
血液循環などの
Because you see where most of Pain likes to be
痛みが最も発生しやすい場所がわかるからです
like in this
このように
thumbs up
いいぞ
That's because the temperature of the feet is relatively low
足の温度が比較的低いためです。
So it is easier to crystallize
結晶化しやすいので
but there are other factors
しかし、他の要因もあります
also cause crystallization
結晶化も引き起こす
so
それで
The factors that cause crystallization are actually
実は結晶化を引き起こす要因は、
some people
人によっては
still working on
まだ取り組んでいます
because
なぜなら
Many people have high uric acid
尿酸値が高い人が多い
but it won't gout
でも痛風にはならない
There are also such patients
そんな患者さんもいらっしゃいます
it has high uric acid
尿酸が高いです
but it won't explain
しかしそれは説明になりません
it won't hurt
痛くないよ
so
それで
What other factors determine
他の要因が決定するもの
will it be sexual
それは性的になりますか
it crystallizes
結晶化する
In addition to the physical factors we know
私たちが知っている物理的要因に加えて
Temperature definitely affects beyond its melting point
温度は融点を超えると確実に影響します
there are other things we don't know very well
他にもよくわかっていないことがあります
I don't know, let me exchange opinions
分からないので意見交換させてください
that's because
それは
i do sports nutrition
私はスポーツ栄養学をやっています
that athlete
あのスポーツ選手
because he's doing this
彼がこれをやっているから
this explosive movement
この爆発的な動き
it produces a lot of halo acids
大量のハロ酸を生成します
When the haloic acid rises
ハロゲン酸が上昇すると
will decrease
減少します
excretion of uric acid
尿酸の排泄
Normal uric acid will partly come out of our urine
正常な尿酸の一部は尿から出てきます
normal situation
通常の状況
But it also reduces its excretion
しかし、排泄量も減少します
so it builds up in the blood
それで血液中に蓄積します
Therefore, it is more likely for this kind of person to experience pain and collapse.
したがって、この種の人は痛みを経験し、倒れる可能性が高くなります。
We say explosive movement
爆発的な動きと言いますが、
What if in this way of speaking
こういう言い方だとどうなるか
Then if we exercise too much
それでは、運動しすぎると
Is it also because some cause some athletes
一部のスポーツ選手が原因でもあるのでしょうか
more prone to infection
感染しやすくなる
This injury results in permanent sports damage
この怪我は永久的なスポーツ障害を引き起こす
Thanks
ありがとう
Although I'm not very...
とてもじゃないけど…
i don't exercise
私は運動しません
My guide is regular exercise
私のガイドは定期的な運動です
Actually it is
実はそうなんです
In fact, after exercising
実は運動後は
body tissue will be injured
体の組織が損傷します
so many athletes
とても多くのスポーツ選手
he is actually now
彼は実際に今います
just after exercising
運動した直後
He likes to eat that high protein
彼はその高たんぱく質を食べるのが好きです
because when you are exercising a lot
なぜなら、たくさん運動しているときは
including your muscles
筋肉も含めて
Muscles do...
筋肉はそうなります...
He... our muscles are sore after exercising
彼...運動後は筋肉痛です
In fact, it's a bit...wrong. You just mentioned that the host finished eating.
実は、それは少し...間違っています。先ほど、ホストが食事を終えたと言いました。
This is where many of our normal machine packs die
これは、通常のマシンパックの多くが機能しなくなる場所です
So you have to eat a lot of albumin and then supplement it
そのため、アルブミンをたくさん食べて、それを補う必要があります。
so you just said nothing wrong
だからあなたは何も間違ったことは言っていない
In fact, that is an over-exercise person.
実は、それは運動しすぎの人なのです。
Because he is the same inside
彼も中身は同じだから
movement from a certain point of view
ある視点から見た動き
Back to the round one I started with
最初のラウンドに戻ります
is the constant state
一定の状態です
your extreme exercise
あなたの極端な運動
In fact, it is also a pressure on the body
実はそれも身体への負担なのです
Stress also produces a so-called steady state
ストレスもいわゆる定常状態を生み出します
So intense exercise can actually produce an inflammatory response
非常に激しい運動は実際に炎症反応を引き起こす可能性があります
there's nothing wrong with that
それは何も問題ありません
so many athletes
とても多くのスポーツ選手
Many people say athletes are healthy
スポーツ選手は健康だという人が多い
Actually, go and see that
実際に行ってみてください
Explain that athletes do not live longer than average
スポーツ選手は平均よりも長生きしないことを説明する
They sometimes say that sports cause different injuries
スポーツはさまざまな怪我を引き起こすと言われることがあります
In fact, it will cause all kinds of occupational injuries
実際、あらゆる種類の労働災害を引き起こす可能性があります
So there is no saying that the movement itself is also
だから、運動そのものもそうだということはありません。
A very important factor that promotes the inflammatory response
炎症反応を促進する非常に重要な因子
It will accelerate the progress of many diseases
多くの病気の進行を加速するでしょう
there is another one, right?
もう一つありますよね？
there are two more
あと2つあります
another one
もう一つ
has a problem
問題があります
You seem to be ready to give me an answer.
あなたは私に答える準備ができているようです。
In my other research, Dean Liu just said that I am also working on a molecule.
私の他の研究で、先ほど学部長リューが私も分子の研究をしていると言いました。
How he put this giant cell it has two types
彼はこの巨大細胞をどのように配置したか、それには2つのタイプがある
It is M1, which is the inflammation of the blood-spraying multi-cell technology that I just mentioned
それがM1、先ほどお話しした血液噴霧マルチセル技術の炎症です。
But another one called M2 basically it's anti-inflammatory
しかし、M2と呼ばれる別のものは基本的に抗炎症作用があります
we did
私たちはやった
We have done a study
私たちは調査を行いました
We have done research and used this flu virus to trigger Diuchen's severe inflammation.
私たちは研究を行い、このインフルエンザウイルスを使ってディウシェンの重度の炎症を引き起こしました。
And then we'll just beat that protein in
そして、そのタンパク質を打ち負かすだけです
Just like you say it makes M1 become M2
あなたの言うとおり、M1 が M2 になります
It is true that its entire inflammatory response is reduced.
炎症反応全体が軽減されるのは事実です。
Then its death rate also decreased
そしたら死亡率も減った
So if your family is interested
ですから、ご家族が興味を持っていただければ、
Give me the memory film, I can show you the Payback meter
思い出のフィルムをください、ペイバックメーターを見せます
really works
本当に機能します
are we the last question
最後の質問ですか
department
デパートメント
and a copy of that scientific magazine
それとその科学雑誌のコピー
still me
まだ私
Oh, good
ああ、いいね
I just talked a lot about the loss of immunity
先ほど免疫力の低下についてお話しましたが、
The sky cannon window and the sky cannon window
スカイキャノンの窓とスカイキャノンの窓
Is there any new progress in these two current materials or research?
これら 2 つの現在の資料や研究に新たな進展はありますか?
i didn't do my homework sorry
宿題をしませんでした、ごめんなさい
Sky gun window in English is Penfix
スカイガンの窓は英語でPenfixです
You are asking a good question. Wenyongs here belongs to the P department.
良い質問ですね。ここのウェニョンは P 部門に所属しています。
Ji Biwen has an expert in the P department here, that is our Liu Wuyan miscellaneous
Ji BiwenにはここのP部門の専門家がいます、それが私たちのLiu Wuyan雑多です
right
右
Liu Wuyan can study Penfix's current Treatment
Liu Wuyan は Penfix の現在の治療法を研究できる
no fact
事実はない
I mean, it's an autoimmune disease.
つまり、自己免疫疾患です。
So it has nothing to do with the cell base storm
つまり、基地の嵐とは何の関係もありません
But it's also about immunity
でもそれは免疫力の問題でもある
so far
これまでのところ
There really aren't that many good self-disciplines
良い自己規律は実際にはそれほど多くありません
That is to rely on the inner stock market
それは内部株式市場に依存することです
Inner stock market or this method of suppressing the immune response
内部株式市場または免疫反応を抑制するこの方法
over there
そちら側
how to use this
これの使い方
How does this immune system cause autoimmunity
この免疫系はどのようにして自己免疫を引き起こすのか
Then treat according to that mechanism
そしてそのメカニズムに沿った治療を行います
In fact there is still a lot of room
実はまだ空きがたくさんあります
So there's a lot more in immunology
免疫学にはさらに多くのことがあります
can be discussed
議論できる
and find some way
そして何らかの方法を見つける
Because these students and teachers just said in the past
なぜなら、これらの生徒と教師が過去にこう言ったからです。
It is said that it is done by the inner stock city
インナーストックシティで行われているそうです
He takes the good and the bad
彼は良いことも悪いことも受け入れる
that's not the best way
それは最善の方法ではありません
But the method so far is to use
しかし、これまでの方法は使用することです
A high amount of domestic stock market will do it
国内株式市場の多額の値上がりがそうなるだろう
right
右
In fact, the disease can be suppressed
実は病気は抑制できる
But let me analyze
でも分析させてください
very interesting
とても興味深い
like i talk a little too much
ちょっと話しすぎたような
Today the protagonist is
今日の主役は、
now to say
今言うこと
It's just that we have a treatment that's not the best
ただ私たちが行っている治療法が最善ではないというだけです
it's not enough by itself
それだけでは十分ではありません
But it can reduce the amount of internal memory used
ただし、使用される内部メモリの量を減らすことができます
is called IVIG
IVIGと呼ばれます
Just take that person's immigrant globulin
その人の移民グロブリンを摂取してください
Just look at it's in the blood
見てください、それは血の中にあります
it is going to
それはそうなるだろう
In the case of a company, 100, 300, or thousands of people will be
企業の場合、100人、300人、あるいは何千人もの人が
The immigrant globulin is separated from Dong Nei's blood
ドンネイの血液から移民グロブリンが分離される
is imcanti
イムカンティです
No, it's IGG
いいえ、IGGです
then hit the patient
それから患者を殴る
I don't know why
どうしてか分かりません
It's going to stop this autoimmune reaction
この自己免疫反応を止めることになります
it can be done over there
あそこでできるよ
current thinking says
現在の考えは言う
It has something to do with the biological blood of that sugar
それはその糖の生物学的血液と関係があります
it can will
それはできる
That is the autoimmunity
それが自己免疫です
right
右
good
良い
Yes or no
はい、もしくは、いいえ
to the scientific man magazine
サイエンスマン誌へ
can share with him
彼と共有できる
another one
もう一つ
there is none left
何も残っていない
OK
OK
It does not matter
それはどうでもいい事です
we are
私たちです
come again or continue
また来るか続けるか
keep talking
話を続ける
let me ask
聞いてもいいですか
that cell storm theory
そのセルストーム理論
Is there any correlation for an antioxidant
抗酸化物質との相関関係はありますか
especially this one
特にこれ
chicken flower
鶏の花
please advise on this
これについてアドバイスしてください
Actually in the pronunciation response
実際に発音反応で
one of the features
特徴の一つ
I just said that inside Cytogenetic Storm
細胞遺伝学的嵐の中でそれを言ったばかりです
One of them includes free muscle
そのうちの1つは自由な筋肉を含みます
free muscle
自由な筋肉
so free muscle
とても自由な筋肉
In fact, it also caused many
実際、それは多くの原因にもなりました
a cause of cell damage
細胞損傷の原因
because it's a lot
たくさんあるから
After becoming a free muscle
フリーマッスルになってから
it will spray water
水を噴霧します
it becomes a whole desoiled
それは全体的に汚れたものになる
it oxidizes many things
多くのものを酸化させます
So it also causes
したがって、それはまた、
cause of injury
怪我の原因
So in the past it was said
それで昔はこう言われてた
Anti-free muscle drugs
抗遊離筋薬
in anti-inflammatory
抗炎症作用で
it works
できます
But it only works for that
でもそれだけで効果があるんだよ
mild inflammation
軽度の炎症
it will work
それが動作します
But for cell-based storms so severe
しかし、これほど深刻な携帯電話ベースの嵐の場合、
That is, its strength compared to the cell base
つまり、細胞ベースと比較した強度です。
it's much weaker
それははるかに弱いです
So just relying on free machines
したがって、無料のマシンに依存するだけです
To treat such a powerful technological storm
このような強力なテクノロジーの嵐に対処するには
The effect is probably very limited
おそらく効果は非常に限定的である
Okay, thank you
大丈夫ありがとう
ok i think this speech will end here
さて、このスピーチはここで終わると思います
then we thank you again
それではまたよろしくお願いします
Thank you professor for your excellent speech
先生、素晴らしい講演をありがとうございました
thank you all thank you
みんなありがとう、ありがとう
Thanks
ありがとう